<aiml>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS AFGHANISTAN</pattern>
        <template>Afghanistān is a country in South Asia. It has borders with Pakistan in the south and east, Iran in the west, Turkmenistan, Uzbekistan and Tajikistan in the north, and China in the far northeast.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT AFGHANISTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS AFGHANISTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT AFGHANISTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS AFGHANISTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ALBANIA</pattern>
        <template>on the European continent    —  Albania is an independent republic in Southeastern Europe, with an area of 28,748 square kilometres. The capital is Tirana, and other important cities are Durrës, Elbasan and Vlora. Over 3 million people live in Albania. The most Albanians are Muslims with 55%, 23% Eastern Orthodox and 15% Roman Catholics.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ALBANIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ALBANIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ALBANIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ALBANIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ALGERIA</pattern>
        <template>Algeria is a country in the Western part of North Africa. The capital city is Algiers. It is the largest country in Africa. The name is from the city of Algiers. It is bordered by the Mediterranean Sea in the north, Tunisia in the northeast, Libya in the east, Niger in the southeast, Mauritania and Mali in the southwest, Western Sahara in the west and Morocco in the northwest.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ALGERIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ALGERIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ALGERIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ALGERIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS AMERICAN SAMOA</pattern>
        <template>American Samoa is a territory of the United States in Samoan Islands, in the South Pacific Ocean.International rivalries in the latter half of the 19th century were settled by an 1899 treaty in which Germany and the US divided the Samoan archipelago. The US formally occupied its portion - a smaller group of eastern islands with the noted harbor of Pago Pago - the following year. The western islands are now the independent state of Samoa. Though technically considered "unorganized" in that the US Congress has not passed an Organic Act for the territory, American Samoa is self-governing under a constitution that became effective on July 1, 1967.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT AMERICAN SAMOA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS AMERICAN SAMOA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT AMERICAN SAMOA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS AMERICAN SAMOA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ANDORRA</pattern>
        <template>on the European continent    —  Andorra is a European country between Spain and France. There are about 84,000 people living in the country. The capital is Andorra la Vella. It is ruled by a Spanish Bishop and the French President. Andorra's government is a parliamentary democracy.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ANDORRA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ANDORRA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ANDORRA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ANDORRA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ANGOLA</pattern>
        <template>Angola is a country in Africa. The capital is Luanda. Angola is in the south of the continent.Angola is a member state of the African Union, the Community of Portuguese Language Countries, the Latin Union, South Atlantic Peace and Cooperation Zone and the Southern African Development Community.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ANGOLA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ANGOLA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ANGOLA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ANGOLA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ANGUILLA</pattern>
        <template>Anguilla is a group of five islands in the Caribbean Sea. The islands are ruled by Great Britain.Anguilla was once part of what is now Saint Kitts and Nevis, but broke away in 1980. Anguilla wanted to still be a part of Great Britain, and Saint Kitts and Nevis wanted to be independent.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ANGUILLA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ANGUILLA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ANGUILLA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ANGUILLA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ANTARCTICA</pattern>
        <template>Antarctica is the Earth's southernmost continent. It is on the South Pole. It's almost entirely south of the Antarctic Circle. Around Antarctica is the Southern Ocean. At 14.0 million km2, it is the fifth-largest continent in area after Asia, Africa, North America, and South America. About 98% of Antarctica is covered by ice. This ice averages at least 1.6 kilometers in thickness.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ANTARCTICA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ANTARCTICA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ANTARCTICA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ANTARCTICA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ANTIGUA AND BARBUDA</pattern>
        <template>Antigua and Barbuda is an island nation in the eastern Caribbean Sea on the boundary with the Atlantic Ocean. Antigua and Barbuda are part of the Lesser Antilles archipelago. In 2011, about 81,800 people lived there. The capital and largest port and city is St. John's, on Antigua. The country used to be a part of the British Empire. The nation still belongs to the British Commonwealth.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ANTIGUA AND BARBUDA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ANTIGUA AND BARBUDA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ANTIGUA AND BARBUDA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ANTIGUA AND BARBUDA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ARGENTINA</pattern>
        <template>Argentina is a country in South America. Argentina is the second-largest country in South America and the eighth-largest country in the world.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ARGENTINA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ARGENTINA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ARGENTINA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ARGENTINA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ARMENIA</pattern>
        <template>Armenia is a country in the western part of Asia. Its capital city is Yerevan. Armenia received its independence from the Soviet Union in 1991.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ARMENIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ARMENIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ARMENIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ARMENIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ARUBA</pattern>
        <template>in the Caribbean  Aruba is an island in the Caribbean Sea, just a short distance north of the Venezuelan Paraguaná Peninsula, and it forms a part of the Kingdom of the Netherlands. Unlike much of the Caribbean region, it has a dry climate and an arid, cactus-strewn landscape. This climate has helped tourism, because visitors to the island can reliably expect warm, sunny weather.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ARUBA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ARUBA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ARUBA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ARUBA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS AUSTRALIA</pattern>
        <template>Australia, officially called the Commonwealth of Australia, is a country and sovereign state in the southern hemisphere, located on its own continent between the Pacific Ocean and the Indian Ocean. Its capital city is Canberra, and its largest city is Sydney.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT AUSTRALIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS AUSTRALIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT AUSTRALIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS AUSTRALIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS AUSTRIA</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Austria, is a country in Central Europe. Around Austria there are Germany, Czech Republic, Slovakia, Hungary, Slovenia, Italy, Switzerland, and Liechtenstein. Currently, the chancellor is Christian Kern. The previous chancellor was Werner Faymann. Austria has been a member-state of the EU since 1995.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT AUSTRIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS AUSTRIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT AUSTRIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS AUSTRIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS AZERBAIJAN</pattern>
        <template>Azerbaijan is a country in the South Caucasus region of Eurasia. It is next to Russia in the north, Georgia, Armenia, in the west, Iran in the south, and Caspian Sea on the east. Its capital city is Baku. Azerbaijan became independent from the Soviet Union when it ended in 1991.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT AZERBAIJAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS AZERBAIJAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT AZERBAIJAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS AZERBAIJAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BAHAMAS</pattern>
        <template>The Bahamas is a group of islands in the West Indies. The country's capital, Nassau, is on New Providence Island.The Taino were the first people living there. In 1492, Christopher Columbus found the Americas by landing on another of the islands, San Salvador. The Eleutheran Adventurers soon came along, making a home in Eleuthera.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BAHAMAS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BAHAMAS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BAHAMAS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BAHAMAS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BAHRAIN</pattern>
        <template>in the Middle East    —  Bahrain is an island nation in the Persian Gulf. Saudi Arabia is to the west and is connected to Bahrain by the King Fahd Causeway, and Qatar is to the south across the Persian Gulf. The Qatar-Bahrain Friendship Bridge, not yet built, will link Bahrain to Qatar as the longest fixed bridge in the world.Qatar and Bahrain's flag is the same design but not the same colors because Qatar is white and maroon and Bahrain is white and red</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BAHRAIN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BAHRAIN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BAHRAIN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BAHRAIN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BANGLADESH</pattern>
        <template>Bangladesh is a country in South Asia. It is next to the North-east Indian provincial regions of India, which converges with Southeast Asia to the east. Its full name is The People's Republic of Bangla-Desh. The capital and the largest city is Dhaka. Bangladesh is surrounded on all three sides by the Republic of India, and Myanmar on the south-eastern corner, it is near the People's Republic of China, Bhutan, Sikkim and Nepal. Its independence was fully realised after it declared it self as independent most of 1971 from Pakistan after a bloody war in which over a million people died. Later by Indian military intervention, by that time the provisional government went into exile in Calcutta, Bengal which they considered their homeland to be under Pakistani military occupation. After the Instrument of Surrender, the Bengali peoples became a sovereign nation and when its founder was released from political imprisonment had returned in 1972. Present-day Bangladesh has an area of 55,049 mi² or and it is bigger than Somalian breakaway territory of Somaliland but is smaller than the Persian state of Tajikistan. It is slightly smaller than comparison to the U.S. state of Iowa or the Indian state of Orissa which are similar in their geographical sizes to Bangladesh region. It ranks Ninety-Secondth out of hundred and ninety-five Sovereign countries by area.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BANGLADESH</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BANGLADESH</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BANGLADESH</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BANGLADESH</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BARBADOS</pattern>
        <template>Barbados is an island country in the Caribbean Sea. The island has an area of about 430 km². Its capital and largest city is Bridgetown. The official language of Barbados is English. Barbados is a popular tourist destination. In 2008, the island had a population of about 284,000 people. About 80,000 live in or around Bridgetown.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BARBADOS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BARBADOS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BARBADOS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BARBADOS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BELARUS</pattern>
        <template>on the European continent    —  Belarus is a country in Eastern Europe. About nine million people live there. Its capital is Minsk. It was part of the Soviet Union until 1991. The president of Belarus has been Alexander Lukashenko since 1994. It is bordered by Russia, Ukraine, Poland, Lithuania and Latvia. Over forty percent of its 207,600 square kilometres is forested.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BELARUS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BELARUS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BELARUS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BELARUS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BELGIUM</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union  Belgium, officially the Kingdom of Belgium, is a federal state in Western Europe. It is a founding member of the European Union. It has the headquarters of the European Union, NATO and some other famous organisations. The capital city of Belgium is Brussels. Belgium has an area of 30,528 square kilometres. Around 11 million people live in Belgium.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BELGIUM</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BELGIUM</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BELGIUM</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BELGIUM</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BELIZE</pattern>
        <template>Belize is a country in Central America. It used to be called British Honduras, but changed its name in 1973. Long before that it was part of the Mayan Empire.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BELIZE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BELIZE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BELIZE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BELIZE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BENIN</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union    —  Benin is a country in Africa. The capital of Benin is Porto-Novo. The seat of government is in Cotonou, the country's largest city. Most people live on the small southern coastline on the Bight of Benin.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BENIN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BENIN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BENIN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BENIN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BERMUDA</pattern>
        <template>Bermuda is a British overseas territory in the North Atlantic Ocean. The land has one main island and 180 smaller islands. Bermuda is a popular tourist place, with mild weather during the winter months.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BERMUDA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BERMUDA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BERMUDA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BERMUDA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BHUTAN</pattern>
        <template>Bhutan is a small country in the Himalaya mountains of South Asia. It is ruled by King Jigme Khesar Namgyel Wangchuck, who has been king since 2006. Bhutan was founded in 1644 by Shabdrung Ngawang Namgyel. The Bhutanese people are proud they have always been an independent country. Bhutan's capital city is Thimphu. The official language is Dzongkha.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BHUTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BHUTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BHUTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BHUTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BOLIVIA</pattern>
        <template>in South America  Bolivia is a country in South America. It is land locked by Brazil, Paraguay, Argentina, Peru, and Chile. Evo Morales became the president of Bolivia in January 2006. The population of Bolivia is 10.67 million.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BOLIVIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BOLIVIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BOLIVIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BOLIVIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BOSNIA AND HERZEGOVINA</pattern>
        <template>Bosnia~Herzegovina or Bosnia-Herzegovina is a country in Southeastern Europe, with an area of 51,197 km2 and 4,600,000 people. Countries around Bosnia and Herzegovina are Croatia, Serbia and Montenegro. The capital is Sarajevo, and other important cities are Banja Luka, Mostar, Zenica and Tuzla.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BOSNIA AND HERZEGOVINA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BOSNIA AND HERZEGOVINA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BOSNIA AND HERZEGOVINA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BOSNIA AND HERZEGOVINA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BOTSWANA</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union    —  Botswana is a country in southern Africa. The capital of Botswana is Gaborone.The countries that boarder Botswana are Zimbabwe, South Africa, and Namibia. It is also possible to travel from Botswana directly into Zambia by crossing the Zambezi River by ferry.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BOTSWANA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BOTSWANA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BOTSWANA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BOTSWANA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BOUVET ISLAND</pattern>
        <template>Bouvet Island is an island in the southern part of the Atlantic Ocean. It is in the sub-antarctic areas, 2500 km south-southwest of the Cape of Good Hope.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BOUVET ISLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BOUVET ISLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BOUVET ISLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BOUVET ISLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BRAZIL</pattern>
        <template>Brazil is a country in South America. It is the world's fifth largest country. The country has about 209 million people. The capital of Brazil is Brasília. Brazil was named after brazilwood. Brazilwood is a tree that once grew very well along the Brazilian coast.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BRAZIL</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BRAZIL</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BRAZIL</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BRAZIL</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BRITISH ANTARCTIC TERRITORY</pattern>
        <template>The British Antarctic Territory is a sector of Antarctica claimed by the United Kingdom and is a British overseas territory. It is a triangle in Antarctica from the South Pole to 60° S latitude between longitudes 20° W and 80° W. The Territory was formed on March 3, 1962, although the UK first claimed this part of the Antarctic in 1908. Before 1962, the area now covered by the Territory comprised three separate dependencies of the Falkland Islands;</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BRITISH ANTARCTIC TERRITORY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BRITISH ANTARCTIC TERRITORY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BRITISH ANTARCTIC TERRITORY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BRITISH ANTARCTIC TERRITORY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BRITISH INDIAN OCEAN TERRITORY</pattern>
        <template>The British Indian Ocean Territory is a dependency of the United Kingdom. It includes many small islands in the Indian Ocean. The largest island is Diego Garcia. However, both India and Mauritius claims the territories, and does not recognise the United Kingdom's authority over the Chagos Archipelago. The Indians do not recognise Anglo annexation of these Cultural Indo-Indian/Indies islands as part of Britain and disputes it's status since 1947.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BRITISH INDIAN OCEAN TERRITORY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BRITISH INDIAN OCEAN TERRITORY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BRITISH INDIAN OCEAN TERRITORY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BRITISH INDIAN OCEAN TERRITORY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>The British Virgin Islands are part of the Virgin Islands, which are chain of islands in the Caribbean. The British Virgin Islands are the Eastern half of the island chain, and they are a British Overseas Territory. The British Virgin Islands has sixteen inhabited and more than twenty uninhabited islands. Over 22,000 people live there, which is many fewer than the neighbouring United States Virgin Islands.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BRUNEI</pattern>
        <template>Brunei is a country in Southeast Asia. It is north of Malaysia. The country is rather landlocked by Malaysia. To the north is the South China Sea and the Philippines to the northeast. The capital of Brunei is Bandar Seri Begawan. The country has a small area and not many people live there. The leader of the country is the Sultan of Brunei. He is one of the richest people in the world, because he owns a lot of oil. The main religion in Brunei is Islam there are also many people who follow Buddhism or Animism. The native languages of Brunei is Malay and English as second language.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BRUNEI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BRUNEI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BRUNEI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BRUNEI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BULGARIA</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Bulgaria is a country in southeastern Europe.The capital and the biggest city is Sofia. Their money is called the lev. The Bulgarian government is a member of the European Union and NATO. Rumen Radev became President in 2017. The population of Bulgaria is a little more than 7 million people.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BULGARIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BULGARIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BULGARIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BULGARIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BURKINA FASO</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union    —  Burkina Faso is a country in West Africa. It used to be called Upper Volta and the name was changed to Burkina Faso in 1984. The country was once ruled by France, but it has been independent since 1960. The capital is Ouagadougou.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BURKINA FASO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BURKINA FASO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BURKINA FASO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BURKINA FASO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS BURUNDI</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union    —  Burundi is a small country in Africa. The capital of Burundi is Bujumbura. The official languages of Burundi are Kirundi and French. There are about eight and a half million people in Burundi. Burundi is one of the poorest countries in the world.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT BURUNDI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BURUNDI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT BURUNDI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS BURUNDI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CAMBODIA</pattern>
        <template>in ASEAN    —  Cambodia or Kampuchea is a country in Southeast Asia. It is near Vietnam, Laos, and Thailand. About 13 million people live in Cambodia. The people of Cambodia are called Cambodians or Kampucheans. Khmer is the official language. The country has recently emerged from a long civil war and the rule of the Khmer Rouge. It is part of ASEAN, Association of South East Asian Nations.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CAMBODIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CAMBODIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CAMBODIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CAMBODIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CAMEROON</pattern>
        <template>Cameroon is a country in west Africa. Its capital is Yaoundé. The largest city in Cameroon is Douala. The population of Cameroon is about 20 million. Cameroon's president is Paul Biya, and the Prime Minister is Philémon Yang. They speak nearly 250 languages in Cameroon. French and English are the official languages.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CAMEROON</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CAMEROON</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CAMEROON</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CAMEROON</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CANADA</pattern>
        <template>Canada (/ˈkænədə/ ; French: ) is a country in North America, located to the north of the United States. Its land reaches from the Atlantic Ocean in the east to the Pacific Ocean in the west and the Arctic Ocean to the north, covering 9.98 million square kilometres, making it the world's second-largest country by total area and the fourth-largest country by land area. It has the world's longest coastline and is the only one to touch three oceans.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CANADA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CANADA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CANADA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CANADA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CAPE VERDE</pattern>
        <template>Cape Verde, also known as Cabo Verde and officially as the República de Cabo Verde, is an island country in Africa. It is a group of islands in the Atlantic Ocean, 570 km off the coast of Western Africa. The islands, covering a combined area of slightly over 4,000 km2, are of volcanic origin.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CAPE VERDE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CAPE VERDE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CAPE VERDE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CAPE VERDE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CAYMAN ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>The Cayman Islands are a territory of the United Kingdom in the Caribbean Sea. The three islands are Grand Cayman, Little Cayman, and Cayman Brac.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CAYMAN ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CAYMAN ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CAYMAN ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CAYMAN ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CENTRAL AFRICAN REPUBLIC</pattern>
        <template>The Central African Republic, is a landlocked country in Central Africa. It is mostly a plateau or high, flat piece of land about 941 metres above the sea. The CAR covers a land area of about 620,000 square kilometres, and has an estimated population of about 4.4 million as of 2008. Bangui is the capital city.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CENTRAL AFRICAN REPUBLIC</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CENTRAL AFRICAN REPUBLIC</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CENTRAL AFRICAN REPUBLIC</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CENTRAL AFRICAN REPUBLIC</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CHAD</pattern>
        <template>Chad, is a landlocked country in Central Africa. The capital is N'Djamena. It was owned by the French until 1960. It suffers from poverty, illness, drought, and armed conflicts. In 2011, the population of Chad was 11,525,000.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CHAD</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CHAD</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CHAD</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CHAD</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CHILE</pattern>
        <template>Chile is a country on the south-western side of South America. The majority of people there speak Spanish.Chile, which claims a part of the Antarctic continent, is the longest country on earth. The Atacama Desert, in the north of the country, is the driest place on earth. The average rainfall there is less than 0.05 mm per year. The center of Chile, with the two cities Santiago and Valparaíso, has a Mediterranean climate with an average temperatures of 28 °C in January and 11 °C in July. In the middle of Chile, the country is very fertile.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CHILE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CHILE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CHILE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CHILE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CHINA</pattern>
        <template>China is a cultural region, an ancient civilization, and a nation in East Asia.The last Chinese Civil War resulted in two different political powers today, even though both governments agree they are one nation:</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CHINA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CHINA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CHINA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CHINA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CHRISTMAS ISLAND</pattern>
        <template>The Territory of Christmas Island is a small island that belongs to Australia. It is in the Indian Ocean, 2600 kms northwest of Perth in Western Australia and 500 km south of Jakarta, Indonesia.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CHRISTMAS ISLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CHRISTMAS ISLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CHRISTMAS ISLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CHRISTMAS ISLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS COLOMBIA</pattern>
        <template>{{vunblistColombia, is a big country in South America. It is in the northwest part of that Continent and it has an area of 1.141.748 km². It is the only South American country with coasts on both oceans.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT COLOMBIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS COLOMBIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT COLOMBIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS COLOMBIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS COMOROS</pattern>
        <template>Comoros is a small island nation in the Indian Ocean. It is between Madagascar and mainland Africa. The capital is Moroni on Grande Comore. The population is about 798,000 people.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT COMOROS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS COMOROS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT COMOROS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS COMOROS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS COOK ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>The Cook Islands are a group of islands in the southern Pacific. They form an independent state, but have strong ties with New Zealand. The 15 small islands have a total land surface of 240 square kilometers. About 18.000 people live on the islands, most of them from tourism. The largest island, Rarotonga, also holds the territory's capital, Avarua.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT COOK ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS COOK ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT COOK ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS COOK ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS COSTA RICA</pattern>
        <template>Costa Rica, is a country in Central America. It is bordered by Nicaragua to the north, Panama to the southeast, the Pacific Ocean to the west, and the Caribbean Sea to the east. The official language of Costa Rica is Spanish. The official currency is the colón. It has enjoyed a long period of peace since the 1948 civil war. Because of its natural beauty and political stability, it is nicknamed the "Switzerland of Latin America". Costa Rica has had no army since December 1, 1948. Instead of spending money on the military, the government spends money on education and health.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT COSTA RICA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS COSTA RICA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT COSTA RICA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS COSTA RICA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CROATIA</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Croatia is a country in Southeastern Europe. Its capital city is Zagreb.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CROATIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CROATIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CROATIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CROATIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CUBA</pattern>
        <template>Cuba is an island country in the Caribbean Sea. The country is made up of the big island of Cuba, the Isla de la Juventud island, and many smaller islands. Havana is the capital of Cuba. It is the largest city. The second largest city is Santiago de Cuba. In Spanish, the capital is called "La Habana". Cuba is near the United States, Mexico, Haiti, Jamaica and the Bahamas. People from Cuba are called Cubans. The official language is Spanish. Cuba is warm all year.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CUBA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CUBA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CUBA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CUBA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CYPRUS</pattern>
        <template>This article is about the island. For the country, see Republic of Cyprus and Northern Cyprus.Cyprus is a Mediterranean island off the coasts of Syria and Turkey. It is the third-largest island in the Mediterranean; Sicily and Sardinia are larger. It is slightly larger than Puerto Rico. Geographically, it is part of Asia and in the Middle East, but for political reasons, it is sometimes counted as being part of Europe. There are two states on the island:</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CYPRUS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CYPRUS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CYPRUS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CYPRUS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS CZECH REPUBLIC</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  The Czech Republic (Czech: Česká republika, pronounced   ) is a country in Central Europe. As of 2 May 2016 the official short name of the country is Czechia. The capital and the biggest city is Prague. The currency is the Czech Crown. 1€ is about 27 CZK. The president of Czechia is Miloš Zeman. Czechia's population is about 10.5 million.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT CZECH REPUBLIC</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CZECH REPUBLIC</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT CZECH REPUBLIC</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS CZECH REPUBLIC</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS DENMARK</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Denmark, officially named the Kingdom of Denmark, is a Nordic country in Northern Europe. It is the furthest south of the Scandinavian countries, to the south of Norway and south-west of Sweden. It has a south border with Germany. It borders both the North Sea to the west and the Baltic Sea to the east. Denmark is a developed country with a large welfare state; In 2006 and 2007, surveys ranked Denmark as "the happiest place in the world," based on standards of health, welfare, and education.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT DENMARK</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS DENMARK</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT DENMARK</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS DENMARK</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS DJIBOUTI</pattern>
        <template>Djibouti is a country on the eastern coast of Africa. Djibouti gained its independence on June 27, 1977. Djibouti had a population of 818,159 at the 2009 census. It is one of the least populous countries in Africa.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT DJIBOUTI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS DJIBOUTI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT DJIBOUTI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS DJIBOUTI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS DOMINICA</pattern>
        <template>The Commonwealth of Dominica is an island nation in the Caribbean Sea. It is an English-speaking country. It is located between the French-speaking territories of Guadeloupe and Martinique. The island measures 751 km² in area. Roseau is its capital. Portsmouth is another main town. Almost 70,000 people live on the island.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT DOMINICA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS DOMINICA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT DOMINICA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS DOMINICA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS DOMINICAN REPUBLIC</pattern>
        <template>The Dominican Republic is a country on the Caribbean island of Hispaniola; the other country on the island is Haiti. Its capital, and largest city, is Santo Domingo. The national language is Spanish.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT DOMINICAN REPUBLIC</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS DOMINICAN REPUBLIC</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT DOMINICAN REPUBLIC</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS DOMINICAN REPUBLIC</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS EAST GERMANY</pattern>
        <template>The German Democratic Republic (German: Deutsche Demokratische Republik ), commonly called East Germany, was founded on October 7,1949, after World War II. It was formed from part of the Soviet occupation zone of Germany, including part of the city of Berlin. It is no longer a nation by itself since the two parts of Germany, East Germany and West Germany, reunified in 1990.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT EAST GERMANY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS EAST GERMANY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT EAST GERMANY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS EAST GERMANY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ECUADOR</pattern>
        <template>Ecuador is a small country in South America. It is along the equator. Ecuador has jungles and mountains like the Andes mountains. On the coast of the Pacific Ocean there are beaches. The capital is Quito in the Andes. Quito is at a high altitude. This makes it hard for some new visitors to breathe. The biggest city is Guayaquil on the coast. Cuenca, Ecuador is famous for its old buildings and colonial architecture. Peru borders Ecuador to the south, and Colombia borders it to the north. The Galápagos Islands in the Pacific Ocean are also part of Ecuador and are famous for lots of animals. Charles Darwin travelled in Galápagos.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ECUADOR</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ECUADOR</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ECUADOR</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ECUADOR</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS EGYPT</pattern>
        <template>Egypt is a country in northeast Africa. Its capital city is Cairo. Egypt is famous for its ancient monuments, such as the Pyramids and the Sphinx.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT EGYPT</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS EGYPT</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT EGYPT</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS EGYPT</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS EL SALVADOR</pattern>
        <template>Mestizo: 80%White: 17%Black: 0%Native american: 1%El Salvador is the smallest and most densely populated country in Central America. The country's capital and largest city is San Salvador. Other important cities are: Santa Ana and San Miguel. El Salvador borders the Pacific Ocean on the south, and the countries of Guatemala to the west and Honduras to the north and east.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT EL SALVADOR</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS EL SALVADOR</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT EL SALVADOR</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS EL SALVADOR</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS EQUATORIAL GUINEA</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union  The Republic of Equatorial Guinea is a nation in west central Africa, and one of the smallest countries in Africa. It borders Cameroon on the north, Gabon on the south and east, and the Gulf of Guinea on the west. In the past, it was the Spanish colony of Spanish Guinea. The country's territory is both on the continent and on islands. The continental part is known as Río Muni. On one island, Bioko, is the capital, Malabo.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT EQUATORIAL GUINEA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS EQUATORIAL GUINEA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT EQUATORIAL GUINEA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS EQUATORIAL GUINEA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ERITREA</pattern>
        <template>Eritrea is a country on the eastern coast of Africa. Its official name is The State of Eritrea.Eritrea is located on the coast on the Red Sea. It is north of the Bab-el-Mandeb and the Horn of Africa. Eritrea has borders with the countries of Sudan, Ethiopia, and Djibouti. The land area of Eritrea is 101,000 km², and it is one of the smallest countries in Africa.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ERITREA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ERITREA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ERITREA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ERITREA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ESTONIA</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Estonia /ɪsˈtoʊniə/ , officially the Republic of Estonia is a small country in the Baltic Region of Northern Europe. The capital city is Tallinn. Estonia's neighbors are Sweden, Finland, Russia and Latvia. Its population is 1,332,893.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ESTONIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ESTONIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ESTONIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ESTONIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ETHIOPIA</pattern>
        <template>Ethiopia is a country in the Horn of Africa. It has one of the most well known histories as a country in Africa and the world. Unlike other African countries, Ethiopia stayed together during the Scramble for Africa, except for 5 years when it was ruled by Italians. Ethiopia used to be called Abyssinia. The word "Ethiopia" is from the Greek word Αἰθιοπία meaning sun light burned face. BNP per capita 1370 $.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ETHIOPIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ETHIOPIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ETHIOPIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ETHIOPIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS FALKLAND ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>The Falkland Islands are a group of islands in the South Atlantic ocean, off the coast of South America. They are an overseas territory of the United Kingdom. Argentina disputes this, and claims their sovereignty.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT FALKLAND ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FALKLAND ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT FALKLAND ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FALKLAND ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS FAROE ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>b. ^  The Faeroes, Greenland and Iceland were formally Norwegian possessions until 1814 despite 400 years of Danish monarchy beforehand. c. ^  Information for Denmark including the Faroe Islands and Greenland.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT FAROE ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FAROE ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT FAROE ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FAROE ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS FIJI</pattern>
        <template>Fiji is a small country in the Pacific Ocean. It has 322 islands. The most important islands are Vanua Levu and Viti Levu. The capital city of Fiji is Suva, and the city with the most people is Nadi. There are about 844,330 people in Fiji. The official languages of Fiji are Fijian, English and Hindustani. Fiji is part of the Pacific Rim. About 313000 speak Fiji Hindi.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT FIJI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FIJI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT FIJI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FIJI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS FINLAND</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Finland is a country in Northern Europe and is a member state of the European Union. Finland is one of the Nordic countries and is also part of Fennoscandia. Finland is located between the 60th and 70th latitudes North. Its neighbours are Sweden to the west, Norway to the north, Russia to the east and Estonia to the south, beyond the sea called Gulf of Finland. Most of western and southern coast is on the shore of the Baltic Sea.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT FINLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FINLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT FINLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FINLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS FRANCE</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union  France, officially the French Republic, is a country in Western Europe. Its capital city is Paris. It is a member of the European Union. It is known for its culture, its many monuments and structures, and places such as the Louvre, the Eiffel Tower, the Arc de Triomphe, Giverny, Mont Saint Michel, Versailles, and Notre Dame de Paris. France is divided into 13 régions that are further subdivided into 101 départements.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT FRANCE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FRANCE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT FRANCE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FRANCE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS FRENCH GUIANA</pattern>
        <template>French Guiana is an overseas department and region of France, on the north Atlantic coast of South America. By land area, it is the second largest region of France and the largest overseas department of France and of the European Union.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT FRENCH GUIANA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FRENCH GUIANA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT FRENCH GUIANA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FRENCH GUIANA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS FRENCH POLYNESIA</pattern>
        <template>French Polynesia is a French "overseas collectivity" with the particular designation of "overseas country" in the southern Pacific Ocean.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT FRENCH POLYNESIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FRENCH POLYNESIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT FRENCH POLYNESIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS FRENCH POLYNESIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GABON</pattern>
        <template>The Gabonese Republic, or Gabon, is a country in Africa. It is located on the equator. It has borders with Equatorial Guinea, Cameroon, and the Republic of the Congo. Its capital is Libreville, which is also the largest city in the country. Gabon has an area of almost 270,000 square kilometres. 1.5 million people live in Gabon.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GABON</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GABON</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GABON</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GABON</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GAMBIA</pattern>
        <template>The Gambia is officially called the Republic of the Gambia. This country is also known as Gambia. It is a country in West Africa. It is surrounded by Senegal. It is the smallest country on mainland Africa.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GAMBIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GAMBIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GAMBIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GAMBIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GEORGIA</pattern>
        <template>Georgia could mean either of two things:</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GEORGIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GEORGIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GEORGIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GEORGIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GERMANY</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union  The Federal Republic of Germany, also called Germany, is a country in Central Europe. The country's full name is sometimes shortened to the FRG.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GERMANY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GERMANY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GERMANY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GERMANY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GHANA</pattern>
        <template>The Republic of Ghana is a country in West Africa. Twenty-three million people live there; its capital is Accra. It is in Western Africa, bordering the Gulf of Guinea, between Côte d'Ivoire and Togo.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GHANA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GHANA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GHANA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GHANA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GIBRALTAR</pattern>
        <template>Gibraltar is an Overseas Territory of the United Kingdom. This means it shares the British King or Queen and has the protection of the British Armed Forces. It is in southwest Europe on the Mediterranean Sea. About 28,000 people live there. They are called Gibraltarians.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GIBRALTAR</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GIBRALTAR</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GIBRALTAR</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GIBRALTAR</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GREECE</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Greece, officially the Hellenic Republic, is a country in Southeastern Europe. Its capital city is Athens.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GREECE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GREECE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GREECE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GREECE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GREENLAND</pattern>
        <template>Greenland is a large Arctic island. It has a population of only 50,000 residents, because of its cold climate. Most of the civilian population lives in the southern part of the island, on the coasts. The capital of Greenland is Nuuk. Greenland is the world's largest island that is not a continent. The island is the least densely populated country in the world, with a density of 0.26 people per square kilometer. </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GREENLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GREENLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GREENLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GREENLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GRENADA</pattern>
        <template>Grenada is an island nation in the Caribbean Sea that received its independence from the United Kingdom in 1974. Its capital is St. George's.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GRENADA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GRENADA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GRENADA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GRENADA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GUADELOUPE</pattern>
        <template>Guadeloupe is part of France in the Caribbean Sea. It is made up of five islands. The capital is Basse-Terre.Arawak Native Americans first lived on the islands. Most died when Europeans came. Guadeloupe was first governed by the French Company of the American Islands. It was then taken over by England, given to Sweden, and given back to France.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GUADELOUPE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUADELOUPE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GUADELOUPE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUADELOUPE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GUAM</pattern>
        <template>Guam is an island in Micronesia in the Pacific Ocean that is part of the United States. It is a territory and not one of the 50 U.S. States. The people that first lived there are called "Chamorros". The capital of Guam is the city of Hagåtña. The largest city is Dededo. Guam has important United States Air Force and Naval bases, which use a lot of Guam's land. Guam also has a lot of tourists.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GUAM</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUAM</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GUAM</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUAM</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GUATEMALA</pattern>
        <template>Guatemala is a country in Central America. It is known for its mixed culture, a product of both Mayan and Spanish cultures, from the colonial period. Guatemala is known for its ever-changing weather, a product of the mountain range which crosses the center of the country. Guatemala has many languages, a total of 23. Because of its natural beauty, it is a popular tourist destination.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GUATEMALA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUATEMALA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GUATEMALA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUATEMALA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GUERNSEY</pattern>
        <template>Guernsey is an island in the English Channel off the coast of Normandy. It is one of the Channel Islands, and is the main administration island of the Bailiwick of Guernsey'. Elizabeth II is the head of state, but it has a government of its own, with its own laws and special status when it comes to taxes. 65,573 people live there.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GUERNSEY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUERNSEY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GUERNSEY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUERNSEY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GUINEA</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union  Guinea, or the Republic of Guinea, is an independent nation in western Africa. They speak French. It's a member of Economic Community of West African States.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GUINEA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUINEA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GUINEA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUINEA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GUINEA-BISSAU</pattern>
        <template>Guinea-Bissau is a country in Africa. The official language is Portuguese, and the capital is Bissau. About 1,442,000 people live in Guinea-Bissau as of 2006. The country was a Portuguese colony in the 19th century. At that time is was called Portuguese Guinea. It became independent in 1973. In 1974, the name of the country's capital was added so that it would not be confused with the neighboring country Guinea.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GUINEA-BISSAU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUINEA-BISSAU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GUINEA-BISSAU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUINEA-BISSAU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS GUYANA</pattern>
        <template>The Co-operative Republic of Guyana is a country in South America. It is one of the most sparsely populated countries in the world. Georgetown is the capital; like most of the country's settlements, it is on a flat coastal plain that goes from northwest to southeast. Venezuela claims the land west of the Essequibo River as part of Guayana Esequiba.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT GUYANA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUYANA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT GUYANA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS GUYANA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS HAITI</pattern>
        <template>Haiti, officially the Republic of Haiti is a country on the Caribbean island of Hispaniola. The other country on the island is the Dominican Republic. Haiti has two official languages: French and Haitian Creole, or "Kreyol", which is a simple version of French mixed with African languages. Its capital city is Port-au-Prince.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT HAITI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS HAITI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT HAITI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS HAITI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS HEARD ISLAND AND MCDONALD ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>Heard Island and McDonald Islands are islands in the Indian Ocean, about two-thirds of the way from Madagascar to Antarctica.The islands are a UNESCO World Heritage Site.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT HEARD ISLAND AND MCDONALD ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS HEARD ISLAND AND MCDONALD ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT HEARD ISLAND AND MCDONALD ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS HEARD ISLAND AND MCDONALD ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS HONDURAS</pattern>
        <template>Honduras is a country in Central America. Its capital is Tegucigalpa. Most people of Honduras speak the Spanish language. 7,483,763 people live in Honduras and it is 112,492 square kilometres in size. It is next to El Salvador. To one side is the Caribbean Sea and to the other in the Pacific Ocean.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT HONDURAS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS HONDURAS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT HONDURAS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS HONDURAS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS HUNGARY</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Hungary is a country in Central Europe. Its capital city is Budapest. Hungary is slightly bigger than its western neighbour Austria and has about 10 million inhabitants. Other countries that border Hungary are Slovakia, Ukraine, Romania, Serbia, Croatia and Slovenia. Hungary's official language is the Hungarian language. It has been a member of the European Union since 2004. In Hungarian the country is called Magyarország or Magyar Köztársaság. This is named after the Magyar tribes who came to Hungary in the late 9th century.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT HUNGARY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS HUNGARY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT HUNGARY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS HUNGARY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ICELAND</pattern>
        <template>on the European continent    —  Iceland is an island country in the North Atlantic, between Greenland and Norway, formerly a possession of Denmark. It is culturally considered to be part of Europe. Iceland is 301 kilometres east of Greenland and 1001 kilometres west of Norway. There are about 329,100 people who live in Iceland. Iceland has an area of 103,000 km².</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ICELAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ICELAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ICELAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ICELAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS INDIA</pattern>
        <template>.inThe Republic of India is a country in Asia. It is at the center of South Asia. India has more than 1.2 billion people, which is the second largest population in the world. It is the seventh largest country in the world by area and the largest country in South Asia. It is also the most populous democracy in the world.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT INDIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS INDIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT INDIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS INDIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS INDONESIA</pattern>
        <template>Indonesia is a country in Southeast Asia and Australasia/Oceania. It is part of the Malay Archipelago. It has 18,108 islands. People live on about 6,000 of these islands. The most important islands of Indonesia are Java, Bali, Borneo, Sulawesi, and Sumatra. The capital of Indonesia is Jakarta, on Java. The president now is Joko Widodo. Modern Indonesia began on the 17th of August 1945. At 10 o'clock on that Friday morning, Ir. Soekarno read Indonesia's Declaration of Independence. Indonesia's Independence Day is a national holiday.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT INDONESIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS INDONESIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT INDONESIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS INDONESIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS IRAN</pattern>
        <template>Iran, once known as Persia, is a country in Western Asia. It is part of the Middle East region. It shares borders with Afghanistan, Armenia, Azerbaijan, Iraq, Pakistan, Turkey, and Turkmenistan.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT IRAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS IRAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT IRAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS IRAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS IRAQ</pattern>
        <template>Iraq is a country in southwestern Asia. Iraq borders with Saudi Arabia and Kuwait to the south, Turkey to the north, Syria to the north-west, Jordan to the west, and Iran to the east. The capital of Iraq is Baghdad.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT IRAQ</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS IRAQ</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT IRAQ</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS IRAQ</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS IRELAND</pattern>
        <template>Ireland is an island in Europe. To the west of Ireland is the Atlantic Ocean; to the east of Ireland, across the Irish Sea, is the island of Great Britain.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT IRELAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS IRELAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT IRELAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS IRELAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ISLE OF MAN</pattern>
        <template>in the Irish Sea between England · Scotland · Wales and Northern Ireland  The Isle of Man is an island in the Irish Sea, off the coast of Great Britain. Douglas is the capital city. It also has a flag with a red background and 3 armoured legs joined together - "whichever way you throw us, we always land on our feet".</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ISLE OF MAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ISLE OF MAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ISLE OF MAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ISLE OF MAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ISRAEL</pattern>
        <template>The State of Israel is a country in southwestern Asia on the eastern side of the Mediterranean Sea. Israel became an independent country in 1948. Israel is the only Jewish country, and Jews all over the world think of Israel as their spiritual home. Israel's population was 8.1 million people in 2013 and 6.04 million are Jewish. Almost all the other citizens of Israel are Arab and include Muslims, Christians, Druze, and Samaritans. Israel's largest city is Jerusalem. Israel says that its capital is Jerusalem, but most countries do not agree with that. Most countries keep embassies in Tel Aviv.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ISRAEL</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ISRAEL</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ISRAEL</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ISRAEL</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ITALY</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Italy is a country in Europe and a member of the European Union. Its official name is Repubblica Italiana. Italy is a democratic republic and is a founding member of the European Union.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ITALY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ITALY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ITALY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ITALY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS JAMAICA</pattern>
        <template>Jamaica is an island country in the Caribbean; it is part of the Greater Antilles. The island, 10,990 square kilometres in area, lies about 145 kilometres south of Cuba, and 191 kilometres west of Hispaniola. Its capital is Kingston; other towns include Montego Bay, St. Ann's Bay and Spanish Town. The island is divided into three counties – Cornwall, Middlesex and Surrey – which are subdivided into 14 parishes: Kingston, St. Andrew, St. Catherine, Clarendon,Manchester, St. Elizabeth, Westmoreland, Hanover, St. James, Trelawny, St. Ann, St. Mary, Portland and St. Thomas.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT JAMAICA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS JAMAICA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT JAMAICA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS JAMAICA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS JAPAN</pattern>
        <template>Japan is a country in East Asia. It is a group of many islands close to the east coast of Korea, China and Russia. The Pacific Ocean is to the east of Japan and the Sea of Japan is to the west. Most people in Japan live on one of four of the islands. The biggest of these islands, Honshu, has the most people. Honshu is the 7th largest island in the world. Tokyo is the capital of Japan and its biggest city.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT JAPAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS JAPAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT JAPAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS JAPAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS JERSEY</pattern>
        <template>Jersey is an island off the northwest coast of France. It is a crown dependency of the British monarchy. Jersey is called a bailiwick because the person who is the head of law for the island is called the Bailiff. The Bailiwick of Jersey also includes the islands of the Minquiers and Ecréhous, where nobody lives. The other islands of the Channel Islands belong to the Bailiwick of Guernsey. The country code is JE.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT JERSEY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS JERSEY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT JERSEY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS JERSEY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS JORDAN</pattern>
        <template>English, French, Circassian Jordan is a country in the Middle East. Its official name is The Hashemite Kingdom of Jordan. Also Jordan is know to the people of cheam as a horse admirer</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT JORDAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS JORDAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT JORDAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS JORDAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS KAZAKHSTAN</pattern>
        <template>Kazakhstan is a country in the middle of Eurasia. Its official name is the Republic of Kazakhstan. Kazakhstan is the ninth biggest country in the world, and it is also the biggest landlocked country in the world. Before the end of the Soviet Union, it was called "Kazakh Soviet Socialist Republic". The president of the country since 1991 is called Nursultan Nazarbayev. Astana is the capital city of Kazakhstan. Almaty was the capital until 1998, when it moved to Astana.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT KAZAKHSTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS KAZAKHSTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT KAZAKHSTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS KAZAKHSTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS KENYA</pattern>
        <template>Kenya is a country in East Africa, about half way down, near the horn of Africa. It has the Indian Ocean to its east and Lake Victoria to its west. Kenya borders the nations of Somalia, Ethiopia, South Sudan, Uganda, and Tanzania. Kenya is about the size of France, and almost as large as Texas.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT KENYA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS KENYA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT KENYA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS KENYA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS KIRIBATI</pattern>
        <template>Kiribati is a country in the Pacific Ocean. It has 33 atolls, groups of tiny islands. The country is near the equator. Its capital is South Tarawa, on the Tarawa atoll.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT KIRIBATI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS KIRIBATI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT KIRIBATI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS KIRIBATI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS KUWAIT</pattern>
        <template>Kuwait is a small country in the Middle East.Kuwait is the most socially progressive country in the Gulf region. It has a small and rich economy. It has about 96 billion barrels of crude oil reserves. Crude oil reserves are the oil that is still under the ground and has not yet been cleaned up. Kuwait has 10% of all of the oil reserves in the world. The country makes a lot of money by selling oil. This money is almost half of all the money the country makes. The oil money is also 95% of the money made by selling things to different countries. Also, the oil money is 80% of the money the government makes. Kuwait is now talking with oil companies of other countries to make oil fields in the northern part of the country.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT KUWAIT</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS KUWAIT</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT KUWAIT</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS KUWAIT</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS KYRGYZSTAN</pattern>
        <template>Kyrgyzstan, formally the Kyrgyz Republic, and sometimes known as Kirghizia, is a country in Central Asia. The country is landlocked and mountainous. It has borders with China, Kazakhstan, Tajikistan, and Uzbekistan. Its capital is Bishkek. It was a socialist republic of the Soviet Union, but became independent in 1991. The country was peaceful in the 1990s. Its president, Askar Akayev showed an autocratic and authoritarian character.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT KYRGYZSTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS KYRGYZSTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT KYRGYZSTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS KYRGYZSTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS LAOS</pattern>
        <template>in ASEAN    —  Unitary communist andLao People's Democratic Republic, or Laos country for short, is a country in southeast Asia. The capital of Laos is Vientiane.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT LAOS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LAOS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT LAOS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LAOS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS LATVIA</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Latvia is a country in Northern Europe. The capital is Riga. It is one of the Baltic States, together with Estonia in the north and Lithuania in the south. Latvia's neighbours to the east are the countries Russia and Belarus. Latvia is split into four parts called Kurzeme, Vidzeme, Zemgale, and Latgale.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT LATVIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LATVIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT LATVIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LATVIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS LEBANON</pattern>
        <template>Lebanon is a country in the Middle East, on the Mediterranean Sea. It has a border with Israel to the south, and Syria to the east and north. Lebanon has been independent since 1943. Its capital city is Beirut.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT LEBANON</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LEBANON</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT LEBANON</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LEBANON</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS LESOTHO</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union  Lesotho is a small country in southern Africa. Its population is about 1,800,000. The capital of Lesotho is called Maseru.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT LESOTHO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LESOTHO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT LESOTHO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LESOTHO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS LIBERIA</pattern>
        <template>The Republic of Liberia is a small country on the coast of West Africa. The country has been badly affected in recent years by two civil wars. There are about 3,300,000 in Liberia. The capital city of Liberia is Monrovia.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT LIBERIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LIBERIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT LIBERIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LIBERIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS LIBYA</pattern>
        <template>Libya, officially the State of Libya, is a country in North Africa. It is bordered by the Mediterranean Sea to the north, Egypt to the east, Sudan to the southeast, Chad and Niger to the south, and Algeria and Tunisia to the west. It covers an area of almost 1.8 million square kilometres. It is the 17th largest country in the world.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT LIBYA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LIBYA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT LIBYA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LIBYA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS LIECHTENSTEIN</pattern>
        <template>on the European continent    —  Liechtenstein is a country in Western Europe. It is the sixth smallest country in the world and, with Uzbekistan, one of only two doubly landlocked countries. This means that it is landlocked by a landlocked country. Liechtenstein is between Austria and Switzerland. It was a part of the Holy Roman Empire until 1806 when it became an independent principality.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT LIECHTENSTEIN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LIECHTENSTEIN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT LIECHTENSTEIN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LIECHTENSTEIN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS LITHUANIA</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Lithuania is a country in northern Europe on the eastern shore of the Baltic Sea. Lithuania is a member of the European Union, NATO, and several other organizations.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT LITHUANIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LITHUANIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT LITHUANIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LITHUANIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS LUXEMBOURG</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Luxembourg is a country in Western Europe; its official name is the Grand Duchy of Luxembourg. It is a small country in land area. It was one of the first countries in the European Union. It is also a member of the Benelux. The countries next to Luxembourg are Belgium, Germany, and France. In 2015, its population was 569,700, making it one of Europe's most densely populated countries.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT LUXEMBOURG</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LUXEMBOURG</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT LUXEMBOURG</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS LUXEMBOURG</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MACEDONIA</pattern>
        <template>Macedonia or Macedonian may refer to:</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MACEDONIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MACEDONIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MACEDONIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MACEDONIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MADAGASCAR</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union  MalagasyMadagascar is a large island nation in the Indian Ocean. It is off of the east coast of Africa. Twenty-two million people live there; its capital is Antananarivo. It is the world's fourth largest island.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MADAGASCAR</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MADAGASCAR</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MADAGASCAR</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MADAGASCAR</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MALAWI</pattern>
        <template>Malawi is a country in south-east Africa. It has borders with the countries of Tanzania, Zambia, and Mozambique. The capital of Malawi is Lilongwe and the spoken languages are English and Chichewa. The official language of Malawi is English. The total size is about 118480 km² and there are about 100 people per km². The country is also called "The Warm Heart of Africa". Malawi is one of the smallest countries in Africa. Lake Malawi takes about a third of Malawi's area.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MALAWI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MALAWI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MALAWI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MALAWI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MALAYSIA</pattern>
        <template>Malaysia is a country in Southeast Asia. It is a federation which has 13 states. It is divided into two parts by the South China Sea. Its mainland is on the Malay Peninsula. It faces the Straits of Malacca on its west coast and the South China Sea on its east coast. The other part of this country, sometimes known as East Malaysia, is on the northern part of the island of Borneo in the South China Sea. Kuala Lumpur on the Malay Peninsula is its capital. The federal capital was recently moved to Putrajaya, a newly created city exclusively designed for administration.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MALAYSIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MALAYSIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MALAYSIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MALAYSIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MALDIVES</pattern>
        <template>The Maldives are a group of islands in the Indian Ocean. They are southwest of India. They are made up of the Maldive and Suadive archipelagos, with over 1,200 islands. These islands are a part of 26 atolls. People live on about 200 of the islands. It has more than 1126 coral reefs. It is the flattest country in the world. The highest point in the Maldives is only 2 m high above the level of the sea.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MALDIVES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MALDIVES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MALDIVES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MALDIVES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MALI</pattern>
        <template>Mali is a landlocked country in West Africa. Mali borders Algeria to the north, Niger on the east, Burkina Faso and the Côte d'Ivoire on the south, Guinea on the south-west, and Senegal and Mauritania on the west. Physical features of Mali include the Sahara desert in the north, with the Niger River and Sénégal River in the southern part of the country. As of a July 2011 estimate, Mali has a population of approximately 14,000,000 people. Mali has a total area of 1,220,190 square kilometres. Most of the people live in the southern part of the country, with Mali's capital and most populated city being Bamako.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MALI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MALI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MALI</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MALI</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MALTA</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Malta is an island located in Europe. It is near the center of the Mediterranean Sea, south of Sicily. The capital of Malta is Valletta. About 400,000 people live in Malta. Malta is one of the most densely populated countries in the world. Because of this, it has many cities and towns, that grew close to each other over time.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MALTA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MALTA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MALTA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MALTA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MARSHALL ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>The Republic of the Marshall Islands is a Micronesian island nation in the western Pacific Ocean. The capital of Marshall Islands is Majuro.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MARSHALL ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MARSHALL ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MARSHALL ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MARSHALL ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MARTINIQUE</pattern>
        <template>Martinique is an island in the Caribbean Sea, and is an overseas region of France. It has an area of 1,128 km². Nearly 400,000 people live there.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MARTINIQUE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MARTINIQUE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MARTINIQUE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MARTINIQUE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MAURITANIA</pattern>
        <template>Mauritania is a country in northwest Africa. The capital city, which is also the biggest city in the country, is Nouakchott. It is on the Atlantic coast. Its president is General Mohamed Oueld Abdel-Aziz.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MAURITANIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MAURITANIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MAURITANIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MAURITANIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MAURITIUS</pattern>
        <template>The Republic of Mauritius is an African country. Port Louis is its capital. Mauritius is also the name of the main island the country is on. In the 2000 census, the country had a population of 1,178,848 people.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MAURITIUS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MAURITIUS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MAURITIUS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MAURITIUS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MAYOTTE</pattern>
        <template>Mayotte is an island in the Indian Ocean next to Madagascar. It is geographically part of the Comoros Islands, but politically, it is part of France.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MAYOTTE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MAYOTTE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MAYOTTE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MAYOTTE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS METROPOLITAN FRANCE</pattern>
        <template>Metropolitan France is the part of France that is in Europe. It can also be described as mainland France plus the island of Corsica. By contrast, Overseas France is the collective name for all of the French overseas departments, territories and collectivities and New Caledonia. Metropolitan France and Overseas France together form the French Republic.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT METROPOLITAN FRANCE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS METROPOLITAN FRANCE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT METROPOLITAN FRANCE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS METROPOLITAN FRANCE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MEXICO</pattern>
        <template>Mexico (Spanish: México, official name: United Mexican States (Spanish: Estados Unidos Mexicanos,  listen ) is a country in North America. Mexico is south of Texas and other American states. Guatemala and Belize are south of Mexico. Mexico is between the Pacific Ocean and the Gulf of Mexico.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MEXICO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MEXICO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MEXICO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MEXICO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MICRONESIA</pattern>
        <template>Micronesia is an area in Oceania. Many islands in southwest Pacific Ocean are part of it. Micronesia means small islands in ancient Greek language.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MICRONESIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MICRONESIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MICRONESIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MICRONESIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MOLDOVA</pattern>
        <template>Coordinates: 47°N 29°E﻿ / ﻿47°N 29°E﻿ / 47; 29Moldova is a country in Eastern Europe. Its full name is the Republic of Moldova (Romanian: Republica Moldova,  listen .) It used to be called Moldavia.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MOLDOVA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MOLDOVA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MOLDOVA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MOLDOVA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MONACO</pattern>
        <template>Monaco is the second smallest country in the world; about 34,000 people live there. It is near southeastern France, on the Mediterranean Sea in Western Europe. French is the most common language spoken in Monaco. The head of state is Prince Albert II; the government and the prince share power. Tourism is the main industry. People in Monaco pay no income tax.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MONACO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MONACO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MONACO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MONACO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MONGOLIA</pattern>
        <template>Mongolia is a country between China and Russia, in Asia.Mongolia is a landlocked country in East Asia and Central Asia. It borders Russia to the north and the People's Republic of China to the south, east and west. Mongolia's political system is a parliamentary republic.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MONGOLIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MONGOLIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MONGOLIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MONGOLIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MONTENEGRO</pattern>
        <template>on the European continent    —  Montenegro is a country in Southeastern Europe. It is on the Adriatic Sea, between Albania and Croatia to the North. Inland it also has a common border with Serbia, Kosovo and Bosnia and Herzegovina.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MONTENEGRO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MONTENEGRO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MONTENEGRO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MONTENEGRO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MONTSERRAT</pattern>
        <template>Montserrat is a Caribbean island. It is an overseas territory of the United Kingdom. Montserrat got its name from Christopher Columbus in 1493. The governor of Montserrat is Deborah Barnes-Jones. The capital is officially Plymouth, but the government has moved to Brades after a volcano, Chances Peak, destroyed Plymouth in 1995.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MONTSERRAT</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MONTSERRAT</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MONTSERRAT</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MONTSERRAT</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MOROCCO</pattern>
        <template>Kingdom of Morocco is a country in North Africa.Morocco , officially known as the Kingdom of Morocco , is a sovereign country located in the Maghreb region of North Africa. Geographically, Morocco is characterized by a rugged mountainous interior, large tracts of desert, and a lengthy coastline along the Atlantic Oceanand Mediterranean Sea.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MOROCCO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MOROCCO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MOROCCO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MOROCCO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS MOZAMBIQUE</pattern>
        <template>in the African Union  Mozambique, officially the Republic of Mozambique, is a country in southeastern Africa. Its capital is Maputo. There are about 19 million people. In 1975, Mozambique became independent from Portugal. The country was named Moçambique by the Portuguese after the Island of Mozambique which was the capital of Portuguese Africa. After independence from Portugal it became the People's Republic of Mozambique. There was a big civil war from 1977 to 1992.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT MOZAMBIQUE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MOZAMBIQUE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT MOZAMBIQUE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS MOZAMBIQUE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NAMIBIA</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union  The Republic of Namibia is a country in southern Africa on the Atlantic coast. It is bordered by Angola, Zambia, and Zimbabwe to the north, Botswana to the east, and South Africa to the south. It gained independence from South Africa in 1990. Before that it was called South West Africa. Its capital is Windhoek.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NAMIBIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NAMIBIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NAMIBIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NAMIBIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NAURU</pattern>
        <template>– in Oceania   – in Micronesia  ()  —  Nauru is a small island in the Pacific Ocean. It's 42 kilometers south of the equator and has a surface area of 23.3km². This one island is one country. It sells phosphate to Australia. Nauru is the smallest republic in the world. English and Nauruan are the official languages of Nauru. Nauru has no official capital, but its biggest city is Yaren. The current president of Nauru is Baron Waqa. There are 14 districts in Nauru:</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NAURU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NAURU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NAURU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NAURU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NEPAL</pattern>
        <template>Nepal is a country in South Asia bordering the Republic of India and the People's Republic of China. Mount Everest, the highest mountain in the world, is found there, as well as the Himalaya Mountains. 12 of the world's herro highest mountain peaks are in Nepal. It is also the birthplace of Buddha. It has recently become a secular country, but before it was the only Hindu kingdom in the world. Nepal is a very important pilgrimage place for both Hindus and Buddhists. The population of Nepal in 2007 was almost 29 million people. Nepali is the official language, and there are many other regional languages. English and Hindi are widely understood. The capital city of Nepal is Kathmandu which has a population of over two million people. The second largest city is Pokhara. Pokhara is a major tourist attraction of Nepal which is rich in natural beauty. Pokhara includes many lakes, Phewa Tal is one of them.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NEPAL</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NEPAL</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NEPAL</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NEPAL</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NETHERLANDS</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  The Netherlands is a country that is part of of the Kingdom of the Netherlands. Most of it is in Western Europe, but there are also some parts in the Caribbean. More than 17 million people live there. To the north and west of the European part of the Netherlands is the North Sea, and to the east is Germany and to the south is Belgium. The Netherlands is one of the countries that started the European Union. People who live in the Netherlands are called "Dutch". The language of the Netherlands is also called Dutch. The official capital of the Netherlands is Amsterdam. This however, is not the place where the government is seated, which is in The Hague.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NETHERLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NETHERLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NETHERLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NETHERLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NETHERLANDS ANTILLES</pattern>
        <template>The Netherlands Antilles was a country within the Kingdom of the Netherlands. The country was originally a group of six islands in the Caribbean Sea. Some were discovered in 1493 by Christopher Columbus, and some were discovered in 1499 by Alonso de Ojeda.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NETHERLANDS ANTILLES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NETHERLANDS ANTILLES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NETHERLANDS ANTILLES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NETHERLANDS ANTILLES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NEW CALEDONIA</pattern>
        <template>New Caledonia is a "sui generis collectivity" of France, made up of a main island and several smaller islands. It is in the region of Melanesia in the southwest Pacific. At about half the size of Taiwan, it has a land area of 18,575.5 square kilometres. At the 2004 census, 230,789 people lived there. It has an internet country code top-level domain of.nc. The capital and largest city of the territory is Nouméa. The currency is the CFP franc. The inflation rate is -0.6%. The unemployment rate is 17.1%</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NEW CALEDONIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NEW CALEDONIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NEW CALEDONIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NEW CALEDONIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NEW ZEALAND</pattern>
        <template>New Zealand is an island country and a sovereign state in the south-western part of the Pacific Ocean. It is made up of two large islands and many smaller islands. These islands are located to the south-east of Australia.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NEW ZEALAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NEW ZEALAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NEW ZEALAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NEW ZEALAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NICARAGUA</pattern>
        <template>Nicaragua is a country in Central America. It is officially called the Republic of Nicaragua. It has a size of 129,494 square kilometres. It is the largest country in Central America. It borders Honduras to the north and Costa Rica to the south. The capital of the country is Managua. Managua is the third-largest city in Central America. It is also the biggest city of Nicaragua. Almost a quarter of the population lives in the capital city.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NICARAGUA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NICARAGUA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NICARAGUA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NICARAGUA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NIGER</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union  Niger is a person in western Africa. The capital is Niamey, and the official language is French. It is surrounded by Algeria and Libya to the north, Chad to the east, Nigeria and Benin to the south, and Burkina Faso and Mali to the west. Niger is landlocked, meaning it has no coastline. Niger gets its name from the Black people. My bottom lip bigger then my top lip cause I’m a niga</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NIGER</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NIGER</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NIGER</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NIGER</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NIGERIA</pattern>
        <template>Nigeria is a country in west Africa. It has a population of 188,500,000, which is more than any other country in Africa. The capital of Nigeria is Abuja. Nigeria is known for being a large country, and one of the richest in Africa.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NIGERIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NIGERIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NIGERIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NIGERIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NIUE</pattern>
        <template>Niue is an island country in the south Pacific. Situated between Tonga, Samoa and the Cook Islands, it is commonly known as "Rock of Polynesia". It has its own government, but it is an associated state of New Zealand. This means that Niue's head of state is New Zealand's sovereign in right, and most diplomatic relations are conducted by the latter on Niue's behalf.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NIUE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NIUE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NIUE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NIUE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NORFOLK ISLAND</pattern>
        <template>Norfolk Island is a territory of Australia. It is in the South Pacific Ocean between Australia, New Zealand, and New Caledonia. It was one of the first British settlements in the Pacific. Twice it was used as a penal colony. People from Pitcairn Island were moved to Norfolk Island. It is now a popular place for holidays.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NORFOLK ISLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NORFOLK ISLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NORFOLK ISLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NORFOLK ISLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NORTH KOREA</pattern>
        <template>^  A 2009 constitutional amendment implicitly referred to Kim Jong-il as the "Supreme Leader", as well as the "Chairman of the National Defence Commission". In 2011 Kim Jong-Un was named as the new "Supreme Leader of the party, state and army"</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NORTH KOREA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NORTH KOREA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NORTH KOREA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NORTH KOREA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NORTH VIETNAM</pattern>
        <template>The Democratic Republic of Vietnam, or less commonly, Vietnamese Democratic Republic, also known as North Vietnam, is a former country that existed from 1945 until 1976. It was in the north of present-day Vietnam. It lay north of the local Demilitarized Zone, and South Vietnam lay to the south of it.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NORTH VIETNAM</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NORTH VIETNAM</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NORTH VIETNAM</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NORTH VIETNAM</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NORTHERN MARIANA ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>The Commonwealth of the Northern Mariana Islands is a group of islands in the Pacific Ocean that are a political division controlled by the United States. Its capital is Saipan.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NORTHERN MARIANA ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NORTHERN MARIANA ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NORTHERN MARIANA ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NORTHERN MARIANA ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS NORWAY</pattern>
        <template>on the European continent    —  Norway is a country in the north of Europe. It is the western part of the Scandinavian peninsula. The mainland of Norway is surrounded by a coast on the west side and borders Russia, Finland, and Sweden to the east. The coast touches the Oslofjord, Skagerrak, and the North Sea.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT NORWAY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NORWAY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT NORWAY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS NORWAY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS OMAN</pattern>
        <template>The Sultanate of Oman is a country in the southwestern part of Asia, on the southeast coast of the Arabian Peninsula. It borders the United Arab Emirates to the northwest, Saudi Arabia to the west, and Yemen to the southwest, it also shares a marine border with Pakistan to the north-east. The coast is formed by the Arabian Sea to the south and east, and the Gulf of Oman to the northeast.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT OMAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS OMAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT OMAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS OMAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS PAKISTAN</pattern>
        <template>Pakistan is a country in southern Asia. It is next to India, Iran, Afghanistan, and China. It is officially called the Islamic Republic of Pakistan. It has a long coastline along the Arabian Sea in the south. Pakistan has the fifth largest population in the world. Pakistan has a total land area of 880,940 km2. This makes Pakistan the 34th largest country in the world. Pakistan has the seventh largest army in the world. The capital of Pakistan is Islamabad. Before 1960, it was Karachi, which is now the country's largest city.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT PAKISTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PAKISTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT PAKISTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PAKISTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS PALAU</pattern>
        <template>Palau, officially the Republic of Palau, is an island nation. It is in the Pacific Ocean. Palau is 300 miles east of the Philippines. It got independence from United Nations trusteeship administration in 1994. It is one of the world's youngest and smallest nations. It is sometimes referred to in English under its native name Belau. The capital city of Palau is Melekeok. This has been true since October 1, 2006.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT PALAU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PALAU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT PALAU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PALAU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS PANAMA</pattern>
        <template>Panama is a country in Central America. Its official name is the Republic of Panama, and it is most famous for the Panama Canal. Countries bordering Panama are Costa Rica in the Northwest and Colombia in the Southeast. Panama is between the Caribbean Sea and the Pacific Ocean. Most of the people in Panama are Roman Catholic.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT PANAMA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PANAMA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT PANAMA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PANAMA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS PANAMA CANAL ZONE</pattern>
        <template>Coordinates: 9°07′03.61″N 79°43′12.60″W﻿ / ﻿9.1176694°N 79.7201667°W﻿ / 9.1176694; -79.7201667The Panama Canal Zone is a 553-square-mile former unorganized United States territory. It is now the country of Panama.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT PANAMA CANAL ZONE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PANAMA CANAL ZONE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT PANAMA CANAL ZONE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PANAMA CANAL ZONE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS PAPUA NEW GUINEA</pattern>
        <template>Papua New Guinea is an island country near Indonesia and Australia. It is the east half of New Guinea island, plus some nearby islands. The capital city of Papua New Guinea is Port Moresby. The population of Papua New Guinea are mostly the native population of the island.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT PAPUA NEW GUINEA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PAPUA NEW GUINEA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT PAPUA NEW GUINEA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PAPUA NEW GUINEA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS PARAGUAY</pattern>
        <template>in South America  Paraguay, officially the Republic of Paraguay, is a small country in South America. It is landlocked, meaning that it does not touch the ocean. It is bordered to the North and East by Brazil, the West by Bolivia, and the South and Southeast by Argentina. The main languages are Spanish and Guaraní. Paraguay's population is about 6 million. The ethnic makeup of the population is like the following: Mestizo 80%, European 20%, unmixed Amerindian 1-3%, Asian 1-4%.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT PARAGUAY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PARAGUAY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT PARAGUAY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PARAGUAY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS PERU</pattern>
        <template>Peru is a country in South America. The capital is Lima. The ruins of Machu Picchu, the Andes mountains, and the source of the Amazon River are all found in Peru.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT PERU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PERU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT PERU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PERU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS PHILIPPINES</pattern>
        <template>in ASEAN    —  The Philippines is an Island country in Southeast Asia in the Pacific Ocean. It has 7,641 islands. Spain and the United States, colonized the country. The capital city of the Philippines is Manila.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT PHILIPPINES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PHILIPPINES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT PHILIPPINES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PHILIPPINES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS PITCAIRN ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>The Pitcairn Islands are a group of islands in the southern Pacific. People only live on the second-largest of the four islands. That island is named Pitcairn. It is governed by the United Kingdom. It has the smallest number of people of any country. In 2007, 48 people lived there.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT PITCAIRN ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PITCAIRN ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT PITCAIRN ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PITCAIRN ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS POLAND</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Poland is a country in Central Europe. It is on the east of Germany. The Czech Republic and Slovakia are to the south, Ukraine and Belarus to the east, and the Baltic Sea, Lithuania, and Russia to the north. The total land area of Poland is about 312,679 km2, slightly larger than Oman. This makes Poland the 77th largest country in the world with over 38.5 million people. Most Polish people live in large cities, including the capital, Warsaw, Łódź, Cracow, the second capital of Poland, Szczecin, Gdańsk, Wrocław and Poznań.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT POLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS POLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT POLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS POLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS PORTUGAL</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Portugal is a country in Southern Europe on the Iberian Peninsula. Portugal is the westernmost country of Europe and part of the Mediterranean. It is bordered by the Atlantic Ocean to the west and south and by Spain to the north and east. It has been a member of the European Union since 1986. It was under a dictatorship between 1926 and 1974. It has since prospered but was hit hard by the 2007-2008 recession.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT PORTUGAL</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PORTUGAL</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT PORTUGAL</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PORTUGAL</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS PUERTO RICO</pattern>
        <template>Puerto Rico, also known as the Commonwealth of Puerto Rico, is a territory of the United States in the Caribbean Sea. It has almost 4 million people. It is the 169th largest sized country in the world in amount of land. Its political system is based on a republican system. It has two official languages: Spanish and English. The currency used is the United States dollar. Puerto Rico means "rich port" in Spanish.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT PUERTO RICO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PUERTO RICO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT PUERTO RICO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS PUERTO RICO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS QATAR</pattern>
        <template>Qatar (/ˈkæˌtɑːr/, /ˈkɑːtɑːr/ , /ˈkɑːtər/ or /kəˈtɑːr/ ; Arabic: قطر Qaṭar ; local vernacular pronunciation: ), officially the State of Qatar, is a sovereign country located in Western Asia, occupying the small Qatar Peninsula on the northeastern coast of the Arabian Peninsula. Its sole land border is with Saudi Arabia to the south, with the rest of its territory surrounded by the Persian Gulf. A strait in the Persian Gulf separates Qatar from the nearby island country of Bahrain, as well as sharing maritime borders with the United Arab Emirates and Iran.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT QATAR</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS QATAR</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT QATAR</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS QATAR</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ROMANIA</pattern>
        <template>Romania is a country in southeastern Europe. It is north of the Balkan Peninsula, on the Lower Danube River. Part of Romania is circled by the Carpathian Mountains. It also has a border on the Black Sea. Most of the Danube Delta is found inside Romania. Romania shares borders with Hungary and Serbia to the west, Ukraine to the far northeast, the Republic of Moldova to the near northeast, and Bulgaria to the south.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ROMANIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ROMANIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ROMANIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ROMANIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS RUSSIA</pattern>
        <template>Russia, official name: Russian Federation is a country that is mostly in Asia and partly in Eastern Europe. It is the largest country in the world by land area. About 142.9 million people live in Russia according to the 2010 census. The official name for Russia in English is the Russian Federation. The capital city of Russia is Moscow. Russia shares borders with Norway, Finland, Estonia, Latvia, Lithuania and Poland, Belarus, Ukraine, Georgia, Azerbaijan, Kazakhstan, China, Mongolia, and North Korea. It also has borders over water with Japan by the Sea of Okhotsk, and the United States by the Bering Strait.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT RUSSIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS RUSSIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT RUSSIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS RUSSIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS RWANDA</pattern>
        <template>Rwanda is a country in Africa. It is near Burundi, Congo-Kinshasa, Uganda, and Tanzania. The official language is Kinyarwanda. It is now known mostly because it is the place where the most efficient genocide in history happened.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT RWANDA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS RWANDA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT RWANDA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS RWANDA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS RÉUNION</pattern>
        <template>Réunion is an island of France. It is also a region of France and an overseas department of France, meaning France owns the island nation. It is in the Indian Ocean east of Madagascar, about 200 km southwest of Mauritius. Its capital is Saint-Denis. The highest point in La Reunion is La piton des neiges. The island is also famous for its black beaches, even though people think that there are white beaches. The island is 63 kilometres long; 45 kilometres wide; and covers 2,512 square kilometres. It is similar to the island Hawaii as both are above hotspots in the Earth's crust.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT RÉUNION</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS RÉUNION</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT RÉUNION</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS RÉUNION</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SAINT BARTHÉLEMY</pattern>
        <template>Saint-Barthélemy, officially the Collectivity of Saint-Barthélemy, is a new overseas collectivity of France. It was created on 22 February 2007. It consists of the island of Saint-Barthélemy and neighboring small islands.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SAINT BARTHÉLEMY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT BARTHÉLEMY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SAINT BARTHÉLEMY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT BARTHÉLEMY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SAINT HELENA</pattern>
        <template>Saint Helena is an island of volcanic origin in the South Atlantic Ocean at 15°57′S 5°43′W﻿ / ﻿15.950°S 5.717°W﻿ / -15.950; -5.717. It is named after Saint Helena of Constantinople. It is part of the British Overseas Territory of Saint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da Cunha, which also includes Ascension Island and the islands of Tristan da Cunha. Saint Helena measures about 16 by 8 kilometres and has a population of 4,084.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SAINT HELENA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT HELENA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SAINT HELENA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT HELENA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SAINT KITTS AND NEVIS</pattern>
        <template>The Federation of Saint Kitts and Nevis, is a federal nation made up of two small islands in the Caribbean Sea. It is the smallest independent country in the Western Hemisphere.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SAINT KITTS AND NEVIS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT KITTS AND NEVIS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SAINT KITTS AND NEVIS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT KITTS AND NEVIS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SAINT LUCIA</pattern>
        <template>Saint Lucia is a tropical island country in the eastern Caribbean Sea. It is a part of the Lesser Antilles, and it is north of the islands of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines and south of Martinique. As of 2010 there are about 174,000 people.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SAINT LUCIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT LUCIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SAINT LUCIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT LUCIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SAINT MARTIN</pattern>
        <template>Saint Martin is a tropical island in the northeast Caribbean, approximately 300 km southeast of Puerto Rico. The 87 km² island is divided roughly in half between France and the Netherlands; it is the smallest inhabited sea island divided between two nations.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SAINT MARTIN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT MARTIN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SAINT MARTIN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT MARTIN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SAINT PIERRE AND MIQUELON</pattern>
        <template>Saint Pierre and Miquelon 46°47′N 56°12′W is a French overseas collectivity. It is made up of several small islands. Those islands are near the eastern coast of Canada. They are close to Newfoundland. It is the only thing left of the former colonial territory of New France.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SAINT PIERRE AND MIQUELON</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT PIERRE AND MIQUELON</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SAINT PIERRE AND MIQUELON</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT PIERRE AND MIQUELON</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SAINT VINCENT AND THE GRENADINES</pattern>
        <template>Coordinates: 13°10′N 61°14′W﻿ / ﻿13.167°N 61.233°W﻿ / 13.167; -61.233﻿ Saint Vincent and the Grenadines is an island nation in the Caribbean Sea. It is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations, the Organisation of Eastern Caribbean States and CARICOM.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SAINT VINCENT AND THE GRENADINES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT VINCENT AND THE GRENADINES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SAINT VINCENT AND THE GRENADINES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAINT VINCENT AND THE GRENADINES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SAMOA</pattern>
        <template>The Independent State of Samoa is a country in Pacific Ocean. It became independent from New Zealand in 1962. It has two islands, including Upolu and Savai'i. The capital of Samoa is Apia. It is on the island of Upolu. The head of the country is Malietoa Tanumafili II.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SAMOA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAMOA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SAMOA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAMOA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SAN MARINO</pattern>
        <template>on the European continent    —  San Marino is one of the smallest countries in the world. It is found in southern Europe and is fully surrounded by Italy. Fewer than 30,000 people live there. Its total area is 61 km2. Its capital is the City of San Marino.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SAN MARINO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAN MARINO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SAN MARINO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAN MARINO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SAUDI ARABIA</pattern>
        <template>Saudi Arabia (/ˌsɔːdiː əˈreɪbiə/ , /ˌsaʊ-/ ), officially known as the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia, is an Arab state in Western Asia constituting the bulk of the Arabian Peninsula. With a land area of approximately 2,150,000 km2, Saudi Arabia is geographically the 5th-largest state in Asia and 2nd-largest state in the Arab world after Algeria. Saudi Arabia is bordered by Jordan and Iraq to the north, Kuwait to the northeast, Qatar, Bahrain, and the United Arab Emirates to the east, Oman to the southeast, and Yemen to the south. It is separated from Israel and Egypt by the Gulf of Aqaba. It is the only nation with both a Red Sea coast and a Arabic Gulf coast, and most of its land is dry and barren. Saudi Arabia is the birthplace of Arabs and Islam and sometimes called "the Land of the Two Holy Mosques" in reference to Al-Masjid al-Haram, and Al-Masjid an-Nabawi, the two holiest places in Islam. Arabic is the exclusive official language in Saudi Arabia.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SAUDI ARABIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAUDI ARABIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SAUDI ARABIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SAUDI ARABIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SENEGAL</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union  The Republic of Senegal is a country in West Africa. The capital is Dakar. Senegal covers a land area of almost 197,000 square kilometres. It has population of about 13 million. The climate is tropical with two seasons: the dry season and the rainy cold season. Senegal was given independence by France in 1960.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SENEGAL</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SENEGAL</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SENEGAL</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SENEGAL</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SERBIA</pattern>
        <template>The Republic of Serbia is a country in Southeastern Europe. The capital city is Belgrade. To the north of Serbia is the country Hungary. To the east of Serbia are the countries Bulgaria and Romania. To the south of Serbia are countries Macedonia and Albania. To the west of Serbia are the countries Montenegro, Bosnia and Herzegovina and Croatia.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SERBIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SERBIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SERBIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SERBIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SERBIA AND MONTENEGRO</pattern>
        <template>Serbia and Montenegro was the name of the state union of Serbia and Montenegro. They used to be two separate Yugoslav republics. In 2006, they became their own countries.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SERBIA AND MONTENEGRO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SERBIA AND MONTENEGRO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SERBIA AND MONTENEGRO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SERBIA AND MONTENEGRO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SEYCHELLES</pattern>
        <template>Seychelles is an African country in the Indian Ocean. Its capital city is Victoria. The official languages are Creole, English, and French.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SEYCHELLES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SEYCHELLES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SEYCHELLES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SEYCHELLES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SIERRA LEONE</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union    —  Sierra Leone is a country in West Africa. Its capital is Freetown. The official language is English.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SIERRA LEONE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SIERRA LEONE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SIERRA LEONE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SIERRA LEONE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SINGAPORE</pattern>
        <template>The Republic of Singapore is an island country and city-state at the southern end of the Malay Peninsula in Asia. Singapore is north of the equator. Its closest neighbours are Malaysia and Indonesia. About 5.40 million people live in Singapore, of which 3.31 million are citizens, and most of them are Chinese. In Tamil, an old Indian language, "Singapura", from which Singapore got its name, means "Lion City" commonly ruled by Sultans.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SINGAPORE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SINGAPORE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SINGAPORE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SINGAPORE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SLOVAKIA</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Slovakia is a country with no access to the ocean in Central Europe. It is bordered by Austria in the southwest, Hungary in the south, Ukraine in the east, Poland in the north and Czech Republic in the northwest. Its capital city is Bratislava, the only capital of the world that borders with other two countries. Other main cities are Košice, Banská Bystrica, Žilina, Trenčín, Nitra, Prešov, Bardejov and Trnava. Slovakia is a member of the European Union since 2004 and its official currency is the Euro.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SLOVAKIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SLOVAKIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SLOVAKIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SLOVAKIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SLOVENIA</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union  Slovenia is a country in Southern Europe. The capital and largest city of Slovenia is Ljubljana. Its major language is Slovenian. Its current population is about 2.0 million. Slovenia's leading exports are manufactured goods and aluminium. It is a parliamentary republic It is a member of the European Union and NATO.. The economy of Slovenia is small, open, and export-oriented.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SLOVENIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SLOVENIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SLOVENIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SLOVENIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SOLOMON ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>The Solomon Islands are a group of islands in the South Pacific. They are known for their beauty and for the many languages spoken there. The capital of the Solomon Islands is Honiara.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SOLOMON ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SOLOMON ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SOLOMON ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SOLOMON ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SOMALIA</pattern>
        <template>Somalia is officially the Republic of Somalia. It was previously known as the Somali Democratic Republic. It is shaped like the number seven. It is a country in the Horn of Africa. It is bordered by Djibouti to the northwest, Kenya to the southwest, the Gulf of Aden with Yemen to the north, the Indian Ocean to the east, and Ethiopia to the west.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SOMALIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SOMALIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SOMALIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SOMALIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SOUTH AFRICA</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union  The Republic of South Africa is a country in the southern region of Africa. About fifty-five million people live there. South Africa is next to Namibia, Botswana, Zimbabwe, Mozambique, Lesotho and Swaziland.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SOUTH AFRICA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SOUTH AFRICA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SOUTH AFRICA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SOUTH AFRICA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SOUTH GEORGIA AND THE SOUTH SANDWICH ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>South Georgia and South Sandwich Islands are an overseas territory of the United Kingdom claimed by Argentina. They are in the southern part of the Atlantic Ocean. The territory was started in 1985, before that it was classed as part of the Falkland Islands. The islands do not have a native population, but in 2006 they had around 20 people on the islands. Most of these people were scientists who are at Bird Island, museum staff at Grytviken and the British Government Officer.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SOUTH GEORGIA AND THE SOUTH SANDWICH ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SOUTH GEORGIA AND THE SOUTH SANDWICH ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SOUTH GEORGIA AND THE SOUTH SANDWICH ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SOUTH GEORGIA AND THE SOUTH SANDWICH ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SOUTH KOREA</pattern>
        <template>South Korea is a country in the southern part of the Korean peninsula, in the north east region of Asia. The capital city is Seoul. The official name of South Korea is the Republic of Korea in English, 대한민국 in Korean writing, and 大韓民國 in Chinese characters. About half of the country's people live in its capital city, Seoul, or near the city in the metropolitan area. Korea's Seoul metropolitan area is one of the most populous metropolitan areas in the world. In fact, some sources say it is the second most populous after Tokyo, Japan.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SOUTH KOREA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SOUTH KOREA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SOUTH KOREA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SOUTH KOREA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SPAIN</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union  Spain is a country in Southern Europe. It is in the Iberian Peninsula near Portugal and Gibraltar. France and the country of Andorra are on its northeast side, where the Pyrenees mountains are.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SPAIN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SPAIN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SPAIN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SPAIN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SRI LANKA</pattern>
        <template>The Democratic Socialist Republic of Sri Lanka is a tropical island nation off the southeast coast of the Indian subcontinent. The capital of the country is Sri Jayawardenepura Kotte while the largest city is Colombo.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SRI LANKA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SRI LANKA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SRI LANKA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SRI LANKA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SUDAN</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union  Sudan is a country in Africa. The official name of Sudan is The Republic of Sudan. Its capital is Khartoum.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SUDAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SUDAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SUDAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SUDAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SURINAME</pattern>
        <template>Suriname, or Surinam, Dutch Guiana, Dutch Guyana or Sranang is a country in South America. The official name of the country is Republiek Suriname. It used to be known as Nederlands Guyana, Netherlands Guiana or Dutch Guiana. It is between Guyana and French Guiana. Paramaribo is the capital city. About half a million people live in the country. Suriname became independent from the Netherlands in 1975. Before that, it was a part of the Kingdom of the Netherlands.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SURINAME</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SURINAME</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SURINAME</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SURINAME</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SWAZILAND</pattern>
        <template>– in Africa   – in the African Union  Swaziland is a country in Africa. It is officially the Kingdom of Swaziland, and sometimes called Ngwane or Swatini. Its capital is Mbabane. The country is named after the 19th-century king Mswati II.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SWAZILAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SWAZILAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SWAZILAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SWAZILAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SWEDEN</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union    —  Swedish Official minority languages: Finnish Meänkieli Sami RomaniSweden is a Nordic country in the part of Europe called Scandinavia. Its neighbors are Finland and Norway. Sweden is also connected to Denmark in the south by a bridge. It is a developed country. It is famous for its welfare state. People who live in Sweden are called Swedes.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SWEDEN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SWEDEN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SWEDEN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SWEDEN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SWITZERLAND</pattern>
        <template>on the European continent    —  Switzerland is a small country in Western Europe. The official name of Switzerland is Confoederatio Helvetica. This is Latin and is not often used except for state documents. Switzerland is a federation of even smaller states - 26 cantons.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SWITZERLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SWITZERLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SWITZERLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SWITZERLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SYRIA</pattern>
        <template>Ba'athist Single Party StateSyria is a country in the Middle East, the west part of Asia. It borders on Lebanon, Israel, Jordan, Iraq, and Turkey. Its western part faces the Mediterranean Sea. Its eastern and northern parts are mountainous.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SYRIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SYRIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SYRIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SYRIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS SÃO TOMÉ AND PRÍNCIPE</pattern>
        <template>The Democratic Republic of São Tomé and Príncipe is the second-smallest African country, formed by two islands: São Tomé and Príncipe.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT SÃO TOMÉ AND PRÍNCIPE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SÃO TOMÉ AND PRÍNCIPE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT SÃO TOMÉ AND PRÍNCIPE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS SÃO TOMÉ AND PRÍNCIPE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TAIWAN</pattern>
        <template>98% HanTaiwan, officially the Republic of China, is a region in East Asia. It is the nationalist government of China since its settlement in 1949. It is called the Republic of China which is a special region comprising the island of Taiwan and nearby islands. The Chinese Nationalist government moved to Taiwan after the Communist army took over the capital of Beijing. Currently, the Chinese Nationalist government governs Taipei, the capital of Taiwan. Taiwan is southeast of the China mainland, south of Japan, and north of the Philippines.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TAIWAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TAIWAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TAIWAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TAIWAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TAJIKISTAN</pattern>
        <template>Tajikistan is a country in South-central Asia. It was previously part of the Soviet Union. Tajikistan is a republic. The capital city is Dushanbe. The official language is Tajik,which is a dialect of Farsi.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TAJIKISTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TAJIKISTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TAJIKISTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TAJIKISTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TANZANIA</pattern>
        <template>in the African Union  Dodoma Tanzania is a country in East Africa. The official languages are Kiswahili and English. It is next to Africa's biggest lake, Lake Victoria.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TANZANIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TANZANIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TANZANIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TANZANIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS THAILAND</pattern>
        <template>in ASEAN    —  Thai  • Northeastern Thai  • Central Thai  • Southern Thai Chinese Khmer Malay Tamil Thailand, officially the Kingdom of Thailand (Thai: ราชอาณาจักรไทย, RTGS: Ratcha Anachak Thai; IPA:  ), is a country in Southeast Asia. Its neighbours are Laos, Cambodia, Malaysia, and Myanmar. The country's name was Siam until June 24 1939. It was again called Siam between 1945 and May 11 1949, when it changed back to Thailand. The word Thai comes from the ethnic group in the center of Thailand. The capital city is Bangkok. Thailand is the only country in Southeast Asia that was not ruled by Western countries as it served as a buffer zone between English and French colonies.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT THAILAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS THAILAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THAILAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS THAILAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TIMOR-LESTE</pattern>
        <template>The Democratic Republic of East Timor or Timor Leste is a country in Southeast Asia. It is on the eastern side of the island of Timor, and also the smaller islands of Atauro and Jaco, and a small area, named Oecussi-Ambeno, inside the west side of Timor. That area is an exclave, which means it is separated from the main part of the country by part of another country. That other country is Indonesia.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TIMOR-LESTE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TIMOR-LESTE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TIMOR-LESTE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TIMOR-LESTE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TOGO</pattern>
        <template>Togo is a small country in West Africa. It is bordered by Ghana to the west, Benin to the east and Burkina Faso to the north. The capital city Lomé is located along the Gulf of Guinea. In 2016, about 7.5 million people lived there. The official language is French.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TOGO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TOGO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TOGO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TOGO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TOKELAU</pattern>
        <template>Tokelau is an island group in the Pacific Ocean. It is a territory of New Zealand. Tokelau does not have an official capital. The most important languages spoken in Tokelau are English and Tokelauan. There are about 1,405 people living in Tokelau.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TOKELAU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TOKELAU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TOKELAU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TOKELAU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TONGA</pattern>
        <template>Tonga is a country in Pacific Ocean. It has 169 islands. Only 36 islands have inhabitants. The most important island is Tongatapu. George Tupou V is the king of Tonga and the Prime Minister is ʻAkilisi Pohiva. The capital of Tonga is Nuku'alofa.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TONGA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TONGA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TONGA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TONGA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TRINIDAD AND TOBAGO</pattern>
        <template>The Republic of Trinidad and Tobago is a nation in the south Caribbean Sea. It is 11 km away from Venezuela. The country has two bigger islands, Trinidad and Tobago, and many smaller islands. The capital is Port-of-Spain. The country has about 1,262,366 people in it.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TRINIDAD AND TOBAGO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TRINIDAD AND TOBAGO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TRINIDAD AND TOBAGO</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TRINIDAD AND TOBAGO</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TUNISIA</pattern>
        <template>Tunisia is a country in North Africa. Tunis is its capital.Since history has been recorded, there were Berber tribes living in what is now Tunisia. Most of them built little towns and ports along the coastline so they could trade with different travellers from everywhere in the Mediterranean Sea. Most of the travellers that used to pass by Tunisia were Phoenicians who started to settle on the Tunisian coast during the 10th Century BC. Later, in the 8th Century BC, Carthage was built by some settlers that came from Phoenicia and regions abroad. After many wars against Greece in 6th Century BC, Carthage dominated the Mediterranean Sea.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TUNISIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TUNISIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TUNISIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TUNISIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TURKEY</pattern>
        <template>Turkey is a country in both Europe and Asia. The area of Turkey is about 780,000 square kilometres.Turkey is a republic. There are 81 provinces in Turkey. The money of Turkey is called Turkish Lira. The capital city is Ankara, a city in central Anatolia. The cultural and economic center is in the European side of Istanbul. In the past Istanbul was called Constantinople. The republic was founded in 1923, after World War I and a war of independence. Before that, Turkey was the core of the Ottoman Empire.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TURKEY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TURKEY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TURKEY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TURKEY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TURKMENISTAN</pattern>
        <template>Turkmenistan or Turkmenia is a country in the South-central Asia. It has borders with Afghanistan, Iran, Kazakhstan, Uzbekistan. It has no ocean coastline, but is on the Caspian Sea. The capital of Turkmenistan is Ashghabad.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TURKMENISTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TURKMENISTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TURKMENISTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TURKMENISTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TURKS AND CAICOS ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>in the Caribbean  The Turks and Caicos Islands are two groups of islands in the Caribbean Sea, near the Bahamas. The islands lie southeast of Mayaguana in the Bahamas island chain and north of the island of Hispaniola. Cockburn Town, the capital since 1766, is in the Grand Turk Island about 1,042 kilometres east-southeast of Miami, United States.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TURKS AND CAICOS ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TURKS AND CAICOS ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TURKS AND CAICOS ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TURKS AND CAICOS ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS TUVALU</pattern>
        <template>Tuvalu is a small island country in the Pacific Ocean. In the past, it was the Ellice Islands. It was part of Gilbert and Ellice Islands. It is a monarchy.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT TUVALU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TUVALU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TUVALU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS TUVALU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS U.S. VIRGIN ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>The United States Virgin Islands are a group of islands in the Caribbean Sea. They are currently owned and under the authority of the United States Government. They used to be owned by Denmark. They were sold to the U.S on January 17, 1917, because of fear that the Germans would capture them and use them as a submarine base in World War I. They are the only part of the U.S. where vehicles drive on the left hand side of the road.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT U.S. VIRGIN ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS U.S. VIRGIN ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT U.S. VIRGIN ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS U.S. VIRGIN ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS UGANDA</pattern>
        <template>The Republic of Uganda is a landlocked country in east Africa. Its capital and biggest city is Kampala.The currency is the Ugandan Shilling. The official languages of Uganda are English and Swahili. The most common religion is Christianity. The President of Uganda is Yoweri Kaguta Museveni. The country is to the East of Africa. The population of Uganda is 32 million people. The area of Uganda is about 236,040 km2.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT UGANDA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UGANDA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT UGANDA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UGANDA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS UKRAINE</pattern>
        <template>on the European continent    —  Eastern European Time Further-eastern European Time in the east and Crimea (UTC+2Eastern European Summer Time (UTC+3</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT UKRAINE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UKRAINE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT UKRAINE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UKRAINE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS UNION OF SOVIET SOCIALIST REPUBLICS</pattern>
        <template>2Assigned on 19 September 1990, existing onwards. 3The governments of Estonia, Latvia, and Lithuania view themselves as continuous and unrelated to the respective Soviet republics. Russia views the Estonian, Latvian, and Lithuanian SSR's as legal constituent republics of the USSR and predecessors of the modern Baltic states. The Government of the United States and a number of other countries did not recognize the annexation of Estonia, Latvia, and Lithuania to the USSR as a legal inclusion.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT UNION OF SOVIET SOCIALIST REPUBLICS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UNION OF SOVIET SOCIALIST REPUBLICS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT UNION OF SOVIET SOCIALIST REPUBLICS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UNION OF SOVIET SOCIALIST REPUBLICS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS UNITED ARAB EMIRATES</pattern>
        <template>Coordinates: 24°N 54°E﻿ / ﻿24°N 54°E﻿ / 24; 54in the Arabian Peninsula  The United Arab Emirates or the UAE is a country in the Middle East. It is made up of seven emirates located in the south-eastern part of the Arabian Peninsula, on the south side of the Persian Gulf. It borders Saudi Arabia to the south, Oman to the east, and Qatar to the west.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT UNITED ARAB EMIRATES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UNITED ARAB EMIRATES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT UNITED ARAB EMIRATES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UNITED ARAB EMIRATES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS UNITED KINGDOM</pattern>
        <template>– on the European continent   – in the European Union  The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, simply called the United Kingdom or UK, is a sovereign state in Northern Europe. It is a constitutional monarchy that is made up of four separate countries. It is a member of the European Union, United Nations, the Commonwealth, NATO and the G8. It has the fifth largest economy in the world.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT UNITED KINGDOM</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UNITED KINGDOM</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT UNITED KINGDOM</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UNITED KINGDOM</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS UNITED STATES</pattern>
        <template>The United States of America, often called the United States or America, is a country in North America. It is made up of 50 states, a federal district, and five territories. It has great influence over world finance, trade, culture, military, politics, and technology.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT UNITED STATES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UNITED STATES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT UNITED STATES</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UNITED STATES</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS URUGUAY</pattern>
        <template>Uruguay is a country in South America. The language spoken there is Spanish. Its capital and largest city is Montevideo. Uruguay is bordered by two large neighbors, Brazil and Argentina. The only country in South America that is smaller than Uruguay is Suriname. The land there is mostly flat, and there are many farms in the countryside.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT URUGUAY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS URUGUAY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT URUGUAY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS URUGUAY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS UZBEKISTAN</pattern>
        <template>Uzbekistan is a country in Central Asia. Its capital and largest city is Tashkent. There are about 32 millions people living in Uzbekistan, now. The neighboring countries are Afghanistan, Kazakhstan, Kyrgyzstan, Tajikistan and Turkmenistan. It is a doubly landlocked country, of which there are only two in the world. Most people in Uzbekistan speak a language called Uzbek, a Turkic language similar to Uyghur and Turkish. In the Uzbek language, Uzbekistan is called "O‘zbekiston" and it means "the land of the true nobles". Uzbekistan has a long history. Humans first lived in Uzbekistan from before the 2nd millenium BC. The current president today is Shavkat Mirziyoyev. Human rights in Uzbekistan are 'atrocious' according to Human Rights Watch</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT UZBEKISTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UZBEKISTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT UZBEKISTAN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS UZBEKISTAN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS VANUATU</pattern>
        <template>Vanuatu is a country in the Pacific Ocean. The official languages of Vanuatu are Bislama, English and French. Vanuatu has a population of about 202,609 people. The capital of Vanuatu is Port Vila. The country was ruled as a colony by England and France until it got its freedom in 1980. During the colonial time, it was named the "New Hebrides" or "Nouvelles Hebrides".</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT VANUATU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS VANUATU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT VANUATU</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS VANUATU</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS VATICAN CITY</pattern>
        <template>on the European continent    —  Vatican City (/ˈvætɪkən ˈsɪti/ ; officially Vatican City State, Italian: Stato della Città del Vaticano) is a sovereign state and the smallest country in the world by size, at 0.44 km². Its territory is completely surrounded by Italy and is is only one of three countries in the world that are enclaves of another country. Also, it is the only country in the world that is an enclave of a city, as all of the land around it is part of Rome, the capital of Italy.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT VATICAN CITY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS VATICAN CITY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT VATICAN CITY</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS VATICAN CITY</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS VENEZUELA</pattern>
        <template>Venezuela is a country in northern South America. Its official name is República Bolivariana de Venezuela. The official language is Spanish, and its capital is Caracas. Venezuela produces a large amount of oil every year, and has one of the largest oil supplies in the world.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT VENEZUELA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS VENEZUELA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT VENEZUELA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS VENEZUELA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS VIETNAM</pattern>
        <template>Vietnam is a country in Southeast Asia. The long-form name of the country is the Socialist Republic of Vietnam. The neighboring countries of Vietnam are China, Laos, and Cambodia. Vietnam is one of five remaining countries that believe in communism.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT VIETNAM</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS VIETNAM</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT VIETNAM</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS VIETNAM</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS WAKE ISLAND</pattern>
        <template>Wake Island is an atoll in the Pacific Ocean, near Hawaii. It is controlled by the United States Army and United States Air Force. It is a territory of the United States, part of the United States Minor Outlying Islands. From December 1941 to August 1945 the Empire of Japan ruled Wake Island.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT WAKE ISLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS WAKE ISLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT WAKE ISLAND</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS WAKE ISLAND</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS WALLIS AND FUTUNA</pattern>
        <template>Wallis and Futuna, officially called the Territory of Wallis and Futuna Islands, is a group of three volcanic tropical islands Wallis, Futuna, and Alofi with fringing reefs. They are in the South Pacific Ocean between Fiji and Samoa. One of the islands in the group is named after Cornish explorer Samuel Wallis.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT WALLIS AND FUTUNA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS WALLIS AND FUTUNA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT WALLIS AND FUTUNA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS WALLIS AND FUTUNA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS WESTERN SAHARA</pattern>
        <template>Western Sahara is a territory in Africa. To the north is Morocco, to the east is Algeria, to the south is Mauritania, and to the west is the Atlantic Ocean. Its surface is 266,000 square kilometres. It is one of the most sparsely populated territories in the world. Most of the territory is made of desert flatlands. The largest city is Laâyoune. More than half the population live there. The territory has a population estimated at just more than 500,000.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT WESTERN SAHARA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS WESTERN SAHARA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT WESTERN SAHARA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS WESTERN SAHARA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS YEMEN</pattern>
        <template>The Republic of Yemen or Yemen is a nation in the Middle East. It is the old North Yemen and South Yemen, in the south of the Arabian Peninsula. It borders Saudi Arabia and Oman on the north and the east. To the south is the Arabian Sea, and to the west is the Red Sea. Yemen owns the island of Socotra to the south off the coast of East Africa. A person or thing from Yemen is called Yemeni. Yemen's capital city is Sana'a.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT YEMEN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS YEMEN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT YEMEN</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS YEMEN</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ZAMBIA</pattern>
        <template>The Republic of Zambia is a country in southern Africa. It shares its borders with the Democratic Republic of the Congo to the north, Tanzania to the north-east, Malawi to the east, Mozambique, Zimbabwe, Botswana, and Namibia to the south, and Angola to the west. It was called Northern Rhodesia and it is currently named after the Zambezi River.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ZAMBIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ZAMBIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ZAMBIA</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ZAMBIA</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ZIMBABWE</pattern>
        <template>The Republic of Zimbabwe is a country in the southern part of the continent of Africa. Its capital city is Harare. It is one of the most poor countries and the HID in 2010 was the worst in the world.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ZIMBABWE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ZIMBABWE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ZIMBABWE</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ZIMBABWE</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHERE IS ÅLAND ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>The Åland Islands (Swedish: Åland, Finnish: Ahvenanmaa) form an archipelago in the Baltic Sea. It is situated at the entrance to the Gulf of Bothnia and forms an autonomous, demilitarized, monolingually Swedish-speaking administrative province, region and historical province of Finland. It is the smallest province of Finland, comprising 0.5% of Finland's population and 0.49% of land area. Residents of Åland make up.9% of Finland's population.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ÅLAND ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ÅLAND ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ÅLAND ISLANDS</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHERE IS ÅLAND ISLANDS</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
</aiml>