<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml version="1.0">
    <category>
        <pattern>ROAST ME</pattern>
        <template>
            <random>
                <li>Is your ass jealous of the amount of shit that just came out of your mouth?</li>
                <li>If I wanted to kill myself I'd climb your ego and jump to your IQ.</li>
                <li>Two wrongs don't make a right, take your parents as an example.</li>
                <li>I don't engage in mental combat with the unarmed.</li>
                <li>I'd like to see things from your point of view but I can't seem to get my head that far up my ass.
                </li>
                <li>Your family tree must be a cactus because everybody on it is a prick.</li>
                <li>It's better to let someone think you are an Idiot than to open your mouth and prove it.</li>
                <li>Yo're so ugly, when your mom dropped you off at school she got a fine for littering.</li>
                <li>Your birth certificate is an apology letter from the condom factory.</li>
                <li>If laughter is the best medicine, your face must be curing the world.</li>
                <li>You must have been born on a highway because that's where most accidents happen.</li>
                <li>It looks like your face caught on fire and someone tried to put it out with a hammer.</li>
                <li>The only way you'll ever get laid is if you crawl up a chicken's ass and wait.</li>
                <li>I wasn't born with enough middle fingers to let you know how I feel about you.</li>
                <li>If ignorance is bliss, you must be the happiest person on earth.</li>
                <li>If you really want to know about mistakes, you should ask your parents.</li>
                <li>I'm jealous of all the people that haven't met you!</li>
                <li>Hey, you have something on your chin... no, the 3rd one down.</li>
                <li>You are proof that evolution CAN go in reverse.</li>
                <li>If I had a face like yours, I'd sue my parents.</li>
                <li>What language are you speaking? Cause it sounds like bullshit.</li>
                <li>Don't you love nature, despite what it did to you?</li>
                <li>So, a thought crossed your mind? Must have been a long and lonely journey.</li>
                <li>You're the reason the gene pool needs a lifeguard.</li>
                <li>You're so fake, Barbie is jealous.</li>
                <li>I would love to insult you... but that would be beyond the level of your intelligence.</li>
                <li>Aha, I see the Fuck-Up Fairy has visited us again!</li>
                <li>I don't think you are stupid. You just have a bad luck when thinking.</li>
                <li>I would ask you how old you are but I know you can't count that high.</li>
                <li>As an outsider, what do you think of the human race?</li>
                <li>I'm glad to see you're not letting your education get in the way of your ignorance.</li>
                <li>I don't know what makes you so stupid, but it really works.</li>
                <li>Hell is wallpapered with all your deleted selfies.</li>
                <li>You're so ugly, you scared the crap out of the toilet.</li>
                <li>I don't know what your problem is, but I'll bet it's hard to pronounce.</li>
                <li>I love what you've done with your hair. How do you get it to come out of the nostrils like that?
                </li>
                <li>How many times do I have to flush before you go away?</li>
                <li>You're like school in the summertime - no class.</li>
                <li>You're about as useless as an asshole with tastebuds.</li>
                <li>Oh, what? Sorry. I was trying to imagine you with a personality.</li>
                <li>If bullshit could float...you'd be the Admiral of the fleet!</li>
                <li>Shut up, you'll never be the man your mother is.</li>
                <li>You sound reasonable. It must be time to up my medication!</li>
                <li>You've got two brain cells: one is in a wheelchair and the other one is pushing.</li>
                <li>If shit was music, you'd be an orchestra.</li>
                <li>If your going to be two faced at least make one of them pretty.</li>
                <li>You look like a before picture.</li>
                <li>You are not as bad as people say, you are much, much worse.</li>
                <li>You have the perfect face for radio.</li>
                <li>Whatever kind of look you were going for, you missed.</li>
                <li>Your gene pool could use a little chlorine.</li>
                <li>If I had a dollar for every time you said something smart, I'd be broke.</li>
                <li>Aww, it's so cute when you try to talk about things you don't understand.</li>
                <li>Save your breath... You'll need it to blow up your date.</li>
                <li>I've seen people like you, but I had to pay admission!</li>
                <li>Did your parents keep the placenta and throw away the baby?</li>
                <li>You're street smart. Sesame Street smart.</li>
                <li>When I look into your eyes, I see straight through to the back of your head.</li>
                <li>I'm already visualising the duct tape across your mouth.</li>
                <li>Are you always this stupid or is today a special occasion?</li>
                <li>Your family is just a few clowns short of a circus.</li>
                <li>Are your parents siblings?</li>
                <li>You're as sharp as a bowling ball.</li>
                <li>You look like something I drew with my left hand.</li>
                <li>If my dog had a face like yours I would shave his ass and walk him backwards.</li>
                <li>You have the right to remain silent because whatever you say will probably be stupid anyway.</li>
                <li>You're so sad that even Bob the Builder can't fix your life.</li>
                <li>You're so ugly, even Hello Kitty says goodbye.</li>
                <li>I can't believe that you were the sperm that won the race, and your still slow.</li>
                <li>You are not even beneath my contempt.</li>
                <li>You look like a person that would exchange one of their chromosomes for a Big Mac.</li>
                <li>Idiot college called, they want their mascot back.</li>
                <li>Such a little man, such a drama queen.</li>
                <li>You look like the grinch with plastic surgery gone wrong!</li>
                <li>You would never be able to live down to your reputation, but I see you're doing your best.</li>
                <li>You're about as useful as a bucket without a bottom.</li>
                <li>Your so dense, light must bend around you.</li>
                <li>You better hope you marry rich.</li>
                <li>Looking at you, I understand why some animals eat their young.</li>
                <li>It's like someone took all the bad traits from steve Buschemi and adam Sandler to make your face.
                </li>
                <li>You look like you suck dick for meth and call yourself gay so you sleep better at night.</li>
                <li>Please point to the spot on this doll where the priest touched you.</li>
                <li>9 out of 10 dentists would recommend suicide.</li>
                <li>Your snapchat feed looks like a gender reasignment progression track.</li>
                <li>You have the kind of looks that makes people talk about your charming personality.</li>
                <li>You look like a model from antidepressant commercial.</li>
                <li>I bet you're not allowed within a mile of a school zone.</li>
                <li>Tell me, how does the local football team taste?</li>
                <li>You should become anorectic, then at least there's less of you to be ashamed of.</li>
                <li>You look like you're on the brink of discovering fire.</li>
                <li>I'd give it half a second before I swipe left.</li>
                <li>Looks like you still have the marks on your forehead from your parents' little coathanger
                    experiment.
                </li>
                <li>You look like a ventriloquist dummy used to teach kids the side effects of incest.</li>
                <li>Look at the bright side, your slowly creeping alcoholism will bring your lifespan nicely below the
                    national average.
                </li>
                <li>One night stands are most likely your forte.</li>
                <li>If you stick to the shadows, it's probably not too hard to get picked up.</li>
                <li>
                    <redirect>ROAST ME</redirect>
                    <redirect>ROAST ME</redirect>
                </li>
            </random>
        </template>
    </category>
</aiml>