<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
    <category>
        <pattern>TELL ME ABOUT ([12][0-9][0-9][0-9])</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHAT HAPPENED IN \1</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>EVENTS IN ([12][0-9][0-9][0-9])</pattern>
        <template>
            <redirect>WHAT HAPPENED IN \1</redirect>
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1900</pattern>
        <template>Austrian psychiatrist Sigmund Freud publishes The Interpretation of Dreams. In China, the
            anti-foreigner Boxers occupy Beijing. International force ends both the siege and the Boxer Rebellion.
            Fauvist movement in painting begins, led by Henri Matisse.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1901</pattern>
        <template>Queen Victoria dies on Jan. 22 after a reign of nearly 64 years, and is succeeded by her son, Edward
            VII. The Boxer Rebellion officially ends on Sept. 7 with the signing of the Peace of Beijing.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1902</pattern>
        <template>Enrico Caruso makes his first gramophone recording. Aswan Dam is completed in central Egypt, becoming
            the chief means of storing irrigation water for the Nile valley. Cuba gains independence from Spain.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1903</pattern>
        <template>Panama declares independence from Colombia (Nov. 3). King Alexander of Serbia and his wife are
            assassinated by conspirators (June 10).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1904</pattern>
        <template>Russo-Japanese War begins. As Russia and Japan fight over Manchuria and Korea. Entente Cordiale:
            Britain and France settle their international differences.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1905</pattern>
        <template>In Russo-Japanese War, Port Arthur surrenders to Japanese; Russia suffers other defeats. The Russian
            Revolution of 1905 begins on "Bloody Sunday" when troops fire onto a defenseless group of demonstrators in
            St. Petersburg. Strikes and riots follow. Sailors on Russian battleship Potemkin mutiny; reforms, including
            first Duma, established by Czar Nicholas II’s"October Manifesto."
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1906</pattern>
        <template>Roald Amundsen, Norwegian explorer, locates Magnetic North Pole. Ethiopia declared independent in a
            tripartite pact; country is divided into British, French, and Italian spheres of influence. Finland is the
            first European country to give women the vote.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1907</pattern>
        <template>Second Hague Peace Conference, of 46 nations, adopts 10 conventions on rules of war. The first Cubist
            exhibition is held in Paris.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1908</pattern>
        <template>Earthquake and resulting tsunami kill 70,000 to 100,000 in southern Italy and Sicily. Petroleum
            production starts in Middle East. Mysterious Siberian explosion levels hundreds of square miles of forest.
            Explanations include a comet, meteorite, natural atomic explosion, or crashed UFO.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1909</pattern>
        <template>North Pole reportedly reached by American explorers Robert E. Peary and Matthew Henson. Turkish
            parliament deposes sultan Abd al-Hamid II and replaces him with his brother, Muhammad V. Japan begins
            36-year occupation of Korea. Japanese prince Hirobumi Ito assassinated by Korean nationalist.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1910</pattern>
        <template>Union of South Africa established, with its parliamentary capital in Cape Town and administrative
            capital in Pretoria (May 31). Portuguese monarchy ends. Teofilio Braga is selected as president of new
            republic. Japan formally annexes Korea. Mexican revolution begins; Francisco Madero publishes his manifesto
            La sucesión presidencial en 1910.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1911</pattern>
        <template>First use of aircraft as offensive weapon occurs in Turkish-Italian War. Italy defeats Turks and
            annexes Libya. Chinese Republic proclaimed after revolution overthrows Manchu dynasty. Sun Yat-sen named
            president. Mexican Revolution: Porfirio Diaz, president since 1877, replaced by Francisco Madero. Roald
            Amundsen becomes first man to reach South Pole. U.S. explorer Hiram Bingham discovers Incan city of Machu
            Picchu.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1912</pattern>
        <template>The "unsinkable" oceanliner Titanic sinks on maiden voyage after colliding with an iceberg; over 1,500
            drown (April 15). Balkan Wars begin, resulting from territorial disputes: Turkey defeated by alliance of
            Bulgaria, Serbia, Greece, and Montenegro (Oct.).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1913</pattern>
        <template>Suffragettes demonstrate in London and Washington, D.C. London peace treaty partitions most of
            European Turkey among the victors of first Balkan War. In second Balkan war, Bulgaria attacks Serbia and
            Greece and is defeated after Romania intervenes and Turks recapture Adrianople (June).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1914</pattern>
        <template>World War I begins: Austria declares war on Serbia; Germany on Russia and France; Britain on Germany.
            Austrian Archduke Francis Ferdinand and wife Sophie assassinated in Sarajevo by Serbian nationalist Gavrilo
            Princip. Panama Canal is officially opened after 10 years of construction.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1915</pattern>
        <template>British oceanliner Lusitania sunk by German submarine, 1,195 perish. Second Battle of Ypres is fought.
            Genocide of estimated 600,000 to 1 million Armenians by Turkish soldiers.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1916</pattern>
        <template>Battle of Verdunis fought. Battle of the Somme follows in July. Pershing fails in raid into Mexico in
            quest of rebel Pancho Villa. Easter Rebellion in Ireland put down by British troops.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1917</pattern>
        <template>First U.S. combat troops arrive in France as U.S. declares war on Germany (April 6). Third Battle of
            Ypresis fought. World-wide influenza pandemic strikes; by 1920, nearly 20 million are dead. In U.S. alone,
            500,000 perish. Dutch dancer Mata Hari is convicted and executed as a German spy. Government offices are
            seized and the Romanov's Winter Palace is stormed in Russian October Revolution.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1918</pattern>
        <template>Russian revolutionaries execute the former czar and his family. Russian Civil War between Reds
            (Bolsheviks) and Whites (anti-Bolsheviks); Reds win in 1920. Allied troops (U.S., British, French) intervene
            in Russia (March). Second Battle of the Marne (July-Aug). German Kaiser abdicates (Nov.); hostilities cease
            on the Western Front. Japanese hold Vladivostok until 1922. Worldwide Spanish influenza epidemic strikes; by
            1920, nearly 20 million are dead. In U.S. alone, 500,000 perish.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1919</pattern>
        <template>Versailles Treaty, incorporating Woodrow Wilson's draft Covenant of League of Nations, signed by
            Allies and Germany; rejected by U.S. Senate. 18th Amendment (Prohibition) adopted. Mahatma Gandhi initiates
            Satyagraha campaigns, beginning his nonviolent resistance movement against British rule in India.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1920</pattern>
        <template>U.S. Dept. of Justice "red hunt" nets thousands of radicals; aliens deported. Women's suffrage (19th)
            amendment ratified. Mexican president Venustiano Carranza is assassinated. Treaty of Sèvres dissolves
            Ottoman Empire.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1921</pattern>
        <template>Major treaties signed at Washington Disarmament Conference limit naval tonnage and pledge to respect
            territorial integrity of China.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1922</pattern>
        <template>Mussolini marches on Rome; forms Fascist government. Irish Free State, a self-governing dominion of
            British Empire, officially proclaimed. Reparations Commission fixes German liability at 132 billion gold
            marks. German inflation begins. Kemal Atatürk, founder of modern Turkey, overthrows last sultan.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1923</pattern>
        <template>Adolf Hitler's "Beer Hall Putsch" in Munich fails; in 1924 he is sentenced to five years in prison
            where he writes Mein Kampf. He is released after eight months. Earthquake destroys one-third of Tokyo.
            Occupation of Ruhr by French and Belgian troops to enforce reparations payments.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1924</pattern>
        <template>Death of Lenin; Stalin wins power struggle, rules as Soviet dictator until death in 1953. Italian
            Fascists murder Socialist leader Giacomo Matteotti. Ottoman empire (founded 1290) ends when Turkish
            president Mustafa Kemal ends the caliphate.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1925</pattern>
        <template>Locarno conferences seek to secure European peace by mutual guarantees. John Logie Baird, Scottish
            inventor, transmits human features by television. Adolf Hitler publishes Volume I of Mein Kampf.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1926</pattern>
        <template>A general strike in Britain brings the nation's activities to a standstill. U.S. marines are
            dispatched to Nicaragua during the revolt; they remain until 1933. Chiang Kai-shek becomes leader of China's
            revolutionary party following the 1925 death of Sun Yat-sen. Richard E. Byrd and Floyd Bennett fly from
            Spitsbergen to the North Pole and back.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1927</pattern>
        <template>The German economy collapses. Socialists riot in Vienna; a general strike follows acquittal of Nazis
            for political murder. Trotsky is expelled from the Russian Communist Party. Charles Lindbergh makes the
            first nonstop solo transatlantic flight.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1928</pattern>
        <template>Kellogg-Briand Pact, outlawing war, is signed in Paris by 65 nations. Richard E. Byrd starts an
            expedition to Antarctic; returns in 1930. The first of Joseph Stalin's Five Year Plans imposes
            collectivization on agriculture in the Soviet Union.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1929</pattern>
        <template>Trotsky is expelled from U.S.S.R. The Lateran Treaty establishes an independent Vatican City. First
            large-scale Jewish-Arab violence caused by a clash at the Wailing Wall in Jerusalem.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1930</pattern>
        <template>Britain, U.S., Japan, France, and Italy sign naval disarmament treaty. Nazis gain in German elections.
            Haile Selassie becomes emperor of Ethiopia.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1931</pattern>
        <template>Spain becomes a republic with the overthrow of King Alfonso XIII. British parliament enacts the
            Statute of Westminster, legalizing dominion equality with Britain. Mukden Incident begins Japanese
            occupation of Manchuria. The planned capital of New Delhi opens in India.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1932</pattern>
        <template>Nazis lead in German elections with 230 Reichstag seats. Famine is widespread in U.S.S.R.</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1933</pattern>
        <template>Reichstag fire in Berlin; Nazi terror begins (Feb. 27). Hitler becomes German chancellor (Jan. 30).
            Germany and Japan withdraw from League of Nations.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1934</pattern>
        <template>Chancellor Dollfuss of Austria is assassinated by Nazis. U.S.S.R. admitted to League of Nations.
            Dionne sisters, first quintuplets to survive beyond infancy, born in Canada. Background: Multiple Birth. Mao
            Zedong begins the Long March north with 100,000 soldiers. Hitler becomes Führer when chancellorship and
            presidency are united.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1935</pattern>
        <template>Nazis repudiate Versailles Treaty, introduce compulsory military service. Mussolini invades Ethiopia;
            League of Nations invokes sanctions. Persia becomes Iran under Reza Shah Pahlevi. Nazis enact Nuremberg Laws
            against Jews to prevent "racial pollution." Heinrich Himmler starts breeding program to produce "Aryan super
            race."
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1936</pattern>
        <template>Rome-Berlin Axis is proclaimed (Japan to join in 1940). Spanish civil war begins. Hundreds of
            Americans join the "Lincoln Brigades". Franco's fascist forces defeat Loyalist forces by 1939, when Madrid
            falls. War between China and Japan begins, to continue through World War II. Japan and Germany sign
            anti-Comintern pact; joined by Italy in 1937. Gen. Anastasio Somoza leads a coup d'etat in Nicaragua
            ushering in Somoza family dictatorship for more than 4 decades. King George V dies; succeeded by son, Edward
            VIII, who soon abdicates to marry an American-born divorcée, and is succeeded by brother, George VI.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1937</pattern>
        <template>Italy withdraws from League of Nations. U.S. gunboat Panay sunk by Japanese in Yangtze River. Japan
            invades China, conquers most of coastal area. Britain begins 999 emergency telephone number. The United
            States starts 911 service in New York in 1968.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1938</pattern>
        <template>Hitler marches into Austria; political and geographical union of Germany and Austria proclaimed.
            Munich Pact—Britain, France, and Italy agree to let Germany partition Czechoslovakia. Nazis destroy Jewish
            shops, homes, synagogues in Kristallnacht riots; 20,000-30,000 sent to concentration camps. First oil strike
            in Kuwait transforms the emirate's economy.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1939</pattern>
        <template>Germany invades Poland; occupies Bohemia and Moravia; renounces pact with England and concludes
            10-year non-aggression pact with U.S.S.R. Russo-Finnish War begins; Finns to lose one-tenth of territory in
            1940 peace treaty. World War II begins.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1940</pattern>
        <template>Winston Churchill becomes Britain's Prime Minister. Trotsky is assassinated in Mexico. Estonia,
            Latvia, and Lithuania annexed by U.S.S.R. Hitler invades Denmark, the Netherlands, Belgium, France, and
            Luxembourg. Lascaux caves with Cro-Magnon art discovered by French schoolboy.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1941</pattern>
        <template>Germany attacks the Balkans and Russia. Japanese surprise attack on U.S. fleet at Pearl Harbor brings
            U.S. into World War II; U.S. and Britain declare war on Japan. The first U.S. Lend-Lease shipment of food
            sent to Britain.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1942</pattern>
        <template>Nazi leaders attend the Wannsee Conference to coordinate the "final solution to the Jewish question,"
            the systematic genocide of Jews known as the Holocaust. Declaration of United Nations is signed in
            Washington.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1943</pattern>
        <template>Churchill and Roosevelt hold the Casablanca Conference. Mussolini is deposed and placed under arrest
            (July).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1944</pattern>
        <template>Allies invade Normandy on D-Day (June 6). Bretton Woods Conference creates International Monetary Fund
            and World Bank. Battle of the Bulge begins as Germans penetrate Allied front in Belgium (Dec. 16 to Jan.
            1945). Anne Frank and her family betrayed and sent to concentration camps. She will die in 1945. Dumbarton
            Oaks Conference—U.S., British Commonwealth, and U.S.S.R. propose establishment of United Nations.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1945</pattern>
        <template>Yalta Conference (Roosevelt, Churchill, Stalin) plans final defeat of Germany (Feb). Hitler commits
            suicide (April 30); Germany surrenders (May 7); May 8 is declared V-E Day. Japan signs official surrender on
            V-J Day (Sept. 2). Potsdam Conference (Truman, Churchill, Stalin) establishes basis of German reconstruction
            (July–Aug.). San Francisco Conference establishes the United Nations (April–June). US drops atomic bombs on
            Japanese cities of Hiroshima (Aug. 6) and Nagasaki (Aug. 9).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1946</pattern>
        <template>First meeting of United Nations General Assembly opens in London (Jan. 10). League of Nations
            dissolved (April). Italy abolishes monarchy (June). The Philippines gains independence from the United
            States (July 4). 12 Nazi leaders (including 1 tried in absentia) are sentenced to hang, 7 imprisoned, and 3
            acquitted in the Nuremberg trials (Oct. 1). Winston Churchill's "Iron Curtain" speech warns of Soviet
            expansion. Juan Perón becomes president of Argentina.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1947</pattern>
        <template>Britain nationalizes coal mines (Jan. 1). Peace treaties for Italy, Romania, Bulgaria, Hungary,
            Finland signed in Paris (Feb. 10). Soviet Union rejects US plan for UN atomic-energy control (March 4).
            Marshall Plan proposed to help European nations recover economically from World War II (June). India and
            Pakistan gain independence from Britain (Aug. 15). The Dead Sea Scrolls are discovered at Qumran.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1948</pattern>
        <template>Gandhi assassinated in New Delhi by a Hindu militant (Jan. 30). Communists seize power in
            Czechoslovakia (Feb. 23-25). Organization of American States (OAS) Charter signed at Bogotá, Colombia (April
            30). Nation of Israel proclaimed; British end Mandate at midnight; Arab armies attack (May 14). Berlin
            Airlift begins (June 21); ends May 12, 1949. Stalin and Tito break (June 28). United States of Indonesia
            established as Dutch and Indonesians settle conflict (Dec. 27).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1949</pattern>
        <template>Twelve nations sign the North Atlantic Treaty establishing NATO (Apr. 4). German Federal Republic
            (West Germany) established (Sept. 21). Communist People's Republic of China formally proclaimed by Chairman
            Mao Zedong (Oct. 1). South Africa institutionalizes apartheid. Britain recognizes the independence of the
            Republic of Ireland. Northern Ireland remains a part of the United Kingdom.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1950</pattern>
        <template>Korean War begins when North Korean Communist forces invade South Korea. Sino-Soviet friendship treaty
            signed. Communist Chinese forces invade Tibet. British atomic physicist Klaus Fuchs is convicted of spying
            for the Soviet Union.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1951</pattern>
        <template>Seoul falls first to Communist forces (Jan. 4), then to US-led UN troops (Mar. 14). Despite peace
            talks in July and October, the Korean War continues. Six nations agree to Schuman Plan to pool European coal
            and steel (March 19; in effect Feb. 10, 1953). Japanese peace treaty signed in San Francisco by 49 nations
            (Sept. 8). Libya gains independence from Italy (Dec. 24).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1952</pattern>
        <template>George VI of England dies; his daughter becomes Elizabeth II (Feb. 6). NATO conference approves
            European army (Feb.). King Farouk of Egypt is ousted by a military coup (July 23). General Mohammed Naguib
            assumes power. Britain announces its development of atomic weapons (Oct.). Greece and Turkey join NATO.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1953</pattern>
        <template>Joseph Stalin dies (March 5). Georgi Malenkov becomes Soviet Premier; Lavrenti Beria, Minister of
            Interior; Vyacheslav Molotov, Foreign Minister (March 6). East Berliners rise against Communist rule;
            quelled by tanks (June 17). Korean armistice signed (July 27). Moscow announces explosion of hydrogen bomb
            (Aug. 20). Tito becomes president of Yugoslavia.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1954</pattern>
        <template>Nasser becomes premier of Egypt (April 17). Geneva Conference is convened to bring peace to Vietnam
            (April to July). The country is divided at the 17th parallel, pending democratic elections. Dien Bien Phu,
            French military outpost in Vietnam, falls to Viet Minh army (May 7). Eight-nation Southeast Asia Collective
            Defense Treaty (establishing SEATO) signed at Manila (Sept. 8). Paris agreements grant West Germany
            sovereignty and admittance to NATO and Western European Union (Oct. 23; effective May, 1955). Algerian War
            of Independence against France begins (Oct. 31).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1955</pattern>
        <template>Nikolai A. Bulganin becomes Soviet premier, replacing Malenkov (Feb. 8). Churchill resigns (April 5);
            Anthony Eden succeeds him (April 6). Federal Republic of West Germany becomes a sovereign state (May 5). The
            Soviet Union and seven East European countries sign the Warsaw Pact, a mutual defense treaty (May 14).
            Argentina ousts dictator Juan Perón (Sept. 19). US starts sending $216 million in aid to Vietnam. The US,
            UK, USSR, and France meet at a summit in Geneva.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1956</pattern>
        <template>Nikita Khrushchev, First Secretary of USSR Communist Party, denounces Stalin's excesses (Feb. 24).
            Morocco gains independence from France (March 1) and Spain (April 7). Workers' uprising against Communist
            rule in Poland is crushed (June 28-30). Egypt takes control of Suez Canal (July 26). Israel launches attack
            on Egypt's Sinai peninsula and drives toward Suez Canal (Oct. 29). British and French invade Egypt at Port
            Said (Nov. 5). Cease-fire forced by US pressure stops British, French, and Israeli advance (Nov. 6). Soviet
            troops and tanks crush anti-Communist uprisings in Hungary (November).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1957</pattern>
        <template>Anthony Eden resigns (Jan. 9); MacMillan becomes British Prime Minister. The USSR tests its first
            successful ICBM. Russia launches Sputnik I, first earth-orbiting satellite—the Space Age begins (Oct. 4).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1958</pattern>
        <template>European Economic Community (Common Market) becomes effective (Jan. 1). Egypt and Syria merge into
            United Arab Republic (Feb. 1). Khrushchev becomes Premier of Soviet Union as Bulganin resigns (Mar. 27).
            Gen. Charles de Gaulle becomes French premier (June 1), remaining in power until 1969. Eisenhower orders US
            Marines into Lebanon at request of President Chamoun, who fears overthrow (July 15). New French constitution
            adopted (Sept. 28), de Gaulle elected president of 5th Republic (Dec. 21).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1959</pattern>
        <template>Cuban President Batista resigns and flees (Jan. 1). Fidel Castro assumes power (Feb. 16). Tibet's
            Dalai Lama escapes to India (Mar. 31). Soviet Premier Nikita Khrushchev tours the United States, meeting
            with Eisenhower at Camp David. Britain recognizes the independence of Cyprus.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1960</pattern>
        <template>American U-2 spy plane, piloted by Francis Gary Powers, shot down over Russia (May 1). Khrushchev
            kills Paris summit conference because of U-2 (May 16). Communist China and Soviet Union split in conflict
            over Communist ideology. Senegal, Ghana, Nigeria, Madagascar, and Zaire (Belgian Congo) gain independence.
            There are 900 US military advisers in South Vietnam. Top Nazi murderer of Jews, Adolf Eichmann, captured by
            Israelis in Argentina (May 23)—executed in Israel in 1962.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1961</pattern>
        <template>US breaks diplomatic relations with Cuba (Jan. 3). 1,200 US-sponsored anti-Castro exiles invade Cuba
            at the Bay of Pigs (April 17); the attackers are all killed or captured by Cuban forces. East Germany erects
            the Berlin Wall between East and West Berlin to halt flood of refugees (Aug. 13). USSR detonates 50-megaton
            hydrogen bomb in the largest man-made explosion in history (Oct. 29). There are 2,000 US military advisers
            in South Vietnam. OPEC (Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries) formally constituted.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1962</pattern>
        <template>France transfers sovereignty to new republic of Algeria (July 3). Cuban Missile Crisis: USSR to build
            missile bases in Cuba; Kennedy orders Cuban blockade, lifts blockade after Russia backs down (Aug.-Nov.).
            Pope John XXIII opens Second Vatican Council (Oct. 11). Cuba releases 1,113 prisoners of 1961 invasion
            attempt (Dec. 24). Burundi, Jamaica, Western Samoa, Uganda, and Trinidad and Tobago become independent.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1963</pattern>
        <template>France and West Germany sign treaty of cooperation ending four centuries of conflict (Jan. 22). Pope
            John XXIII dies (June 3), and is succeeded June 21 by Cardinal Montini, who becomes Paul VI. British
            Secretary of War John Profumo resigns in the wake of an affair with Christine Keeler, a teenage showgirl who
            was also involved with the Soviet naval attaché (June). Washington-to-Moscow "hot line" communications link
            opens, designed to reduce risk of accidental war (Aug. 30). Kenya achieves independence. There are 15,000 US
            military advisers in South Vietnam. 32 independent African nations establish the Organization for African
            Unity.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1964</pattern>
        <template>Nelson Mandela sentenced to life imprisonment in South Africa (June 11). Congress approves Gulf of
            Tonkin Resolution after North Vietnamese torpedo boats allegedly attack US destroyers (Aug. 7). Khrushchev
            is deposed; Kosygin becomes premier and Brezhnev becomes first secretary of the Communist Party (October).
            China detonates its first atomic bomb.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1965</pattern>
        <template>The first US combat troops arrive in Vietnam. By the end of the year, 190,000 American soldiers are in
            Vietnam. France withdraws its Atlantic fleet from NATO. Rhodesia unilaterally declares its independence from
            Britain (Nov. 11). US Marines land in the Dominican Republic as fighting persists between rebels and
            Dominican army (April 28).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1966</pattern>
        <template>France withdraws its forces from NATO. President De Gaulle visits the USSR (June 20). Sukarno leaves
            office in Indonesia; Suharto assumes power. Botswana, Lesotho, and Guyana become independent states within
            the British Commonwealth. India suffers the worst famine in 20 years; Lyndon Johnson asks for $1 billion in
            aid to the country.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1967</pattern>
        <template>Biafra secedes from Nigeria (May). Israeli and Arab forces battle; Six-Day War ends with Israel
            occupying Sinai Peninsula, Golan Heights, Gaza Strip and West Bank (June 5). Right-wing military coup
            deposes King Constantine IIof Greece. Communist China announces explosion of its first hydrogen bomb (June
            17). The US and USSR propose a nuclear nonproliferation treaty.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1968</pattern>
        <template>North Korea seizes US Navy ship Pueblo; holds 83 on board as spies (Jan. 23). North Vietnamese launch
            the Tet Offensive, a turning point in the Vietnam War (Jan.-Feb.). American soldiers massacre 347 civilians
            at My Lai (March 16). Czechoslovakia is invaded by Russians and Warsaw Pact forces to crush liberal regime
            (Aug. 20).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1969</pattern>
        <template>Nixon begins "Vietnamization" in Southeast Asia. The United States, USSR, and about 100 other
            countries sign the nuclear nonproliferation treaty (NPT). Russian and Chinese troops clash along the Ussuri
            River. 27-year-old Colonel Muammar al-Qaddafi deposes King Idris of Libya and establishes a pro-Arabic,
            anti-Western, Islamic republic.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1970</pattern>
        <template>Biafra surrenders after 32-month fight for independence from Nigeria (Jan. 12). Rhodesia severs last
            tie with British Crown and declares itself a racially segregated republic (March 1). US troops invade
            Cambodia (May 1). A Palestinian revolt erupts in Jordan. Forces loyal to King Hussein suppress the revolt
            and expel the PLO from the country. Earthquake kills more than 50,000 in Peru (May 31). Egyptian President
            Nasser dies and is replaced by Anwar el-Sadat. Tonga (June 4) and Fiji (Oct. 10) gain independence from
            Britain.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1971</pattern>
        <template>A military junta led by Major General Idi Amin siezes power in Uganda (Jan. 25). Mao Zedong invites
            the US ping-pong team to visit Beijing (Apr. 6). Nixon ends the US trade embargo against China. (Apr. 14).
            Erich Honecker assumes leadership of the East German Communist Party after Walter Ulbricht's resignation
            (May). India and the USSR sign a 20-year friendship pact (Aug. 9). President Mobutu renames the Democratic
            Republic of Congo, establishing Zaire (Oct. 27).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1972</pattern>
        <template>President Nixon makes unprecedented eight-day visit to Communist China and meets with Mao Zedong (Feb.
            17). Britain takes over direct rule of Northern Ireland in bid for peace (March 24). Eleven Israeli athletes
            at Olympic Games in Munich are killed after eight members of an Arab terrorist group invades Olympic
            Village; five guerrillas and one policeman are also killed (Sept. 5). Nixon orders "Christmas bombing" of
            North Vietnam (Dec.).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1973</pattern>
        <template>Great Britain, Ireland, and Denmarkenter European Economic Community (Jan. 1). A ceasefire is signed,
            ending involvement of American ground troops in the Vietnam War. (Jan. 28). US bombing of Cambodia ends,
            marking official halt to 12 years of combat activity in Southeast Asia (Aug. 15). Chile's Marxist president,
            Salvadore Allende, is overthrown (Sept. 11); Gen. Augusto Pinochet takes power. Fourth and largest
            Arab-Israeli conflict begins when Egyptian and Syrian forces attack Israel as Jews mark Yom Kippur, holiest
            day in their calendar (Oct. 6). Egypt and Israel sign US-sponsored cease-fire accord (Nov. 11). Organization
            of Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) hikes oil prices tremendously in retaliation for Western countries'
            involvement in Yom Kippur War.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1974</pattern>
        <template>OPEC ends the oil embargo begun in 1973 during the Yom Kippur War (Mar. 18). Nixon and Brezhnev meet
            in Moscow to discuss arms limitation agreements. Leftist revolution ends almost 50 years of dictatorial rule
            in Portugal (launched Apr. 25). India successfully tests an atomic device, becoming the world's sixth
            nuclear power (May 18). Emperor Haile Selassie of Ethiopia is deposed. A collective military dictatorship
            assumes power (Sept. 12).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1975</pattern>
        <template>Pol Pot and Khmer Rouge take over Cambodia (April). The city of Saigon is surrendered and remaining
            Americans are evacuated, ending the Vietnam War (April 30). American merchant ship Mayaguez, seized by
            Cambodian forces, is rescued in operation by US Navy and Marines, 38 of whom are killed (May 15). Apollo and
            Soyuz spacecraft take off for US-Soviet link-up in space (July 15).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1976</pattern>
        <template>Khmer Rouge leader Pol Pot becomes prime minister (and virtual dictator) of Cambodia after Prince
            Sihanouk steps down (April 2). Israeli airborne commandos attack Uganda's Entebbe Airport and free 103
            hostages held by pro-Palestinian hijackers of Air France plane; one Israeli and several Ugandan soldiers
            killed in raid (July 4). 19-month civil war ends in Lebanon after threatening to escalate to global level
            (Nov.).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1977</pattern>
        <template>Deng Xiaoping, purged Chinese leader, restored to power as Gang of Four is expelled from Communist
            Party (July 22). South African activist Steve Biko dies in police custody (Sept. 12). Nuclear-proliferation
            pact, curbing spread of nuclear weapons, is signed by 15 countries, including US and USSR (Sept. 21).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1978</pattern>
        <template>Rhodesia's Prime Minister Ian D. Smith and three black leaders agree on transfer to black majority
            rule (Feb. 15). US Senate approves Panama Canal neutrality treaty (March 16); votes treaty to turn canal
            over to Panama by year 2000 (April 18). Former Italian Premier Aldo Moro kidnapped by left wing terrorists,
            who kill five bodyguards (March 16); he is found slain (May 9). Pope Paul VI, dead at 80, mourned (Aug. 6);
            new Pope, John Paul I, 65, dies unexpectedly after 34 days in office (Sept. 28); succeeded by Karol Cardinal
            Wojtyla of Poland as John Paul II (Oct. 16). "Framework for Peace" in Middle East signed by Egypt's
            President Anwar Sadat and Israeli Premier Menachem Begin after 13-day conference at Camp David led by
            President Jimmy Carter (Sept. 17). Jim Jones's followers commit mass suicide in Jonestown, Guyana (Nov. 18).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1979</pattern>
        <template>Vietnam and Vietnam-backed Cambodian insurgents announce fall of Cambodian capital Phnom Penh and
            collapse of Pol Pot regime (Jan. 7). Shah leaves Iran after year of turmoil (Jan. 16); revolutionary forces
            under Muslim leader, Ayatollah Ruhollah Khomeini, take over (Feb. 1 et seq.). Carter and Brezhnev sign SALT
            II agreement (June 14). Conservatives win British election; Margaret Thatcher becomes new prime minister
            (May 3). Nicaraguan President General Anastasio Somoza Debayle resigns and flees to Miami (July 17);
            Sandinistas form government (July 19). Iranian militants seize US embassy in Teheran and hold hostages (Nov.
            4). Soviet invasion of Afghanistan stirs world protests (Dec. 27).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1980</pattern>
        <template>Six US embassy aides escape from Iran with Canadian help (Jan. 29). US breaks diplomatic ties with
            Iran (April 7). Eight US servicemen are killed and five are injured as helicopter and cargo plane collide in
            abortive desert raid to rescue American hostages in Teheran (April 25). Iraqi troops hold 90 square miles of
            Iran after invasion; 8-year Iran-Iraq War begins (Sept. 19). Three US nuns and a lay worker are found shot
            in El Salvador (Dec. 4). Anastasio Somoza Debayle, ousted Nicaraguan ruler, and two aides are assassinated
            in Paraguayan capital of Asunción (Sept. 17).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1981</pattern>
        <template>US-Iran agreement frees 52 hostages held in Teheran since 1979 (Jan. 20); hostages welcomed back in US
            (Jan. 25). Pope John Paul II wounded by gunman (May 14). Israel annexes the disputed Golan Heights territory
            (Dec. 14). Egyptian president Anwar el-Sadat is assassinated by Islamic extremists during a military parade
            in Cairo (Oct. 6). President Hilla Limann is overthrown in Ghana as Jerry J. Rawlings seizes power.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1982</pattern>
        <template>British overcome Argentina in Falklands war (April 2-June 15). Israel invades Lebanon in attack on
            PLO. (June 4). Princess Grace, 52, dies of injuries when car plunges off mountain road; daughter Stephanie,
            17, suffers serious injuries (Sept. 14). Lebanese Christian Phalangists kill hundreds of people in two
            Palestinian refugee camps in West Beirut (Sept. 15). Leonid I. Brezhnev, Soviet leader, dies at 75 (Nov.
            10). Yuri V. Andropov, 68, chosen as successor (Nov. 15).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1983</pattern>
        <template>Pope John Paul II signs new Roman Catholic code incorporating changes brought about by Second Vatican
            Council (Jan. 25). Benigno S. Aquino, Jr., 50, political rival of Philippines President Ferdinand Marcos, is
            assassinated in Manila (Aug. 21). South Korean Boeing 747 jetliner bound for Seoul apparently strays into
            Soviet airspace and is shot down by a Soviet SU-15 fighter after it had tracked the airliner for two hours;
            all 269 aboard are killed. (Aug. 30). Terrorist explosion kills 237 US Marines in Beirut (Oct. 23). US
            invades Grenada (Oct. 25).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1984</pattern>
        <template>Syria frees captured US Navy pilot, Lieut. Robert C. Goodman, Jr. (Jan. 3). US and Vatican exchange
            diplomats after 116-year hiatus (Jan. 10). Reagan orders US Marines withdrawn from Beirut international
            peacekeeping force (Feb. 7). Yuri V. Andropov dies at 69; Konstantin U. Chernenko, 72, named Soviet leader
            (Feb. 9). Italy and Vatican agree to end Roman Catholicism as state religion (Feb. 18). Soviet Union
            withdraws from summer Olympic games in US, and other bloc nations follow (May 7 et seq.). José Napoleón
            Duarte, moderate, elected president of El Salvador (May 11). Three hundred slain as Indian Army occupies
            Sikh Golden Temple in Amritsar (June 6). Indian Prime Minister Indira Gandhi assassinated by two Sikh
            bodyguards; 1,000 killed in anti-Sikh riots; son Rajiv succeeds her (Oct. 31). Toxic gas leaks from Union
            Carbide plant in Bhopal, India, killing 2,000 and injuring 150,000 (Dec. 3).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1985</pattern>
        <template>Soviet leader Chernenko dies at 73 and is replaced by Mikhail Gorbachev, 54 (March 11). Under the
            slogans of glasnost and Perestroika, Gorbachev initiates a broad program of reform and liberalization. Two
            Shi'ite Muslim gunmen capture TWA airliner with 133 aboard, 104 of them Americans (June 14); 39 remaining
            hostages freed in Beirut (June 30). PLO terrorists hijack Achille Lauro, Italian cruise ship, with 80
            passengers, plus crew (Oct. 7); American, Leon Klinghoffer, killed (Oct. 8); Italian government toppled by
            political crisis over hijacking (Oct. 16). Reagan and Gorbachev meet at summit (Nov. 19); agree to step up
            arms control talks and renew cultural contacts (Nov. 21). Terrorists seize Egyptian Boeing 737 airliner
            after takeoff from Athens (Nov. 23); 59 dead as Egyptian forces storm plane on Malta (Nov. 24).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1986</pattern>
        <template>Spain and Portugal join European Economic Community (Jan. 1). President Reagan freezes Libyan assets
            in US (Jan. 8). US planes attack Libyan "terrorist centers" (April 14). Haitian President Jean-Claude
            Duvalier flees to France (Feb. 7). President Ferdinand Marcos flees Philippines after ruling for 20 years;
            newly elected Corazon Aquino succeeds him (Feb. 26). Union Carbide agrees to settlement with victims of
            Bhopal gas leak in India (March 22). Major nuclear accident at Soviet Union's Chernobyl power station alarms
            world (April 26 et seq.). Ex-Navy analyst, Jonathan Jay Pollard, 31, guilty as spy for Israel (June 4).
            World Court rules US broke international law in mining Nicaraguan waters (June 27).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1987</pattern>
        <template>William Buckley, American hostage in Lebanon, reported slain (Jan. 20). Iraqi missiles kill 37 in
            attack on US frigate Stark in Persian Gulf (May 17); Iraqi president Hussein apologizes (May 18). Prime
            Minister Thatcher wins rare third term in Britain (June 11). Klaus Barbie, 73, Gestapo wartime chief in
            Lyon, sentenced to life by French court for war crimes (July 4).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1988</pattern>
        <template>US and Canada reach free trade agreement (Jan. 2). Terrorists kill nine tourists on Aegean cruise
            (July 11). Benazir Bhutto, first Islamic woman prime minister, chosen to lead Pakistan (Dec. 1). Pan-Am 747
            explodes from terrorist bomb and crashes in Lockerbie, Scotland, killing all 259 aboard and 11 on ground
            (Dec. 21).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1989</pattern>
        <template>US planes shoot down two Libyan fighters over international waters in Mediterranean (Jan. 4). Iran's
            Ayatollah Khomeini declares author Salman Rushdie's book The Satanic Verses offensive and sentences him to
            death (Feb. 14). Tens of thousands of Chinese students take over Beijing's Tiananmen Square in rally for
            democracy (April 19 et seq.). More than one million in Beijing demonstrate for democracy; chaos spreads
            across nation (mid-May et seq.). Thousands killed in Tiananmen Square as Chinese leaders take hard line
            toward demonstrators (June 4 et seq.). Mikhail S. Gorbachev named Soviet President (May 25). P. W. Botha
            quits as South Africa's President (Aug. 14). Deng Xiaoping resigns from China's leadership (Nov. 9). After
            28 years, Berlin Wall is open to West (Nov. 11). Czech Parliament ends Communists' dominant role (Nov. 30).
            Romanian uprising overthrows Communist government (Dec. 15 et seq.); President Ceausescu and wife executed
            (Dec. 25). US troops invade Panama, seeking capture of General Manuel Noriega (Dec. 20).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1990</pattern>
        <template>General Manuel Noriega surrenders in Panama (Jan. 3). Yugoslav Communists end 45-year monopoly of
            power (Jan. 22). Communist Party relinquish sole power in Soviet government (Feb. 7). South Africa frees
            Nelson Mandela, imprisoned 27½ years (Feb. 11). US-Soviet summit reaches accord on armaments (June 1).
            Western Alliance ends Cold War and proposes joint action with Soviet Union and Eastern Europe (July 6).
            Iraqi troops invade Kuwait, setting off the Persian Gulf War (Aug. 2 et seq.). East and West Germany
            reunited (Aug. 31 et seq.). Margaret Thatcher resigns as British Prime Minister (Nov. 22); John Major
            succeeds her (Nov. 28). Lech Walesa wins Poland's runoff Presidential election (Dec. 9).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1991</pattern>
        <template>Cease-fire ends Persian Gulf War (April 3); UN forces are victorious. Europeans end sanctions on South
            Africa (April 15). South African Parliament repeals apartheid laws (June 5). France agrees to sign 1968
            treaty banning spread of atomic weapons (June 3). China accepts nuclear nonproliferation treaty (Aug. 10).
            Bush-Gorbachev summit negotiates strategic arms reduction treaty (July 31). Communist Government of Albania
            resigns (June 4). Warsaw Pact dissolved (July 1). Boris Yeltsin becomes first freely elected president of
            Russian Republic (July 10). Yeltsin's stock increases when he takes a prominent role in suppressing an
            anti-Gorbachev coup by communist hardliners (Aug. 18-22). Lithuania, Estonia, and Latvia win independence
            from USSR (Aug. 25); US recognizes them (Sept. 2). Haitian troops seize president in uprising (Sept. 30). US
            suspends assistance to Haiti (Oct. 1). US indicts two Libyans in 1988 bombing of Pan Am Flight 103 over
            Lockerbie, Scotland (Nov. 15). Soviet Union breaks up after President Gorbachev's resignation; constituent
            republics form Commonwealth of Independent States (Dec. 25).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1992</pattern>
        <template>Yugoslav Federation broken up (Jan. 15). US recognizes three former Yugoslav republics (April 7). UN
            expels Serbian-dominated Yugoslavia (Sept. 22). Bush and Yeltsin proclaim a formal end to the Cold War (Feb.
            1). US lifts trade sanctions against China (Feb. 21). General Manuel Noriega, former leader of Panama,
            convicted in US court (April 9) and sentenced to 40 years on drug charges (July 10). Russian Parliament
            approves START treaty (Nov. 4). US forces leave Philippines, ending nearly a century of American military
            presence (Nov. 24). Czechoslovak Parliament approves separation into two nations (Nov. 25). UN approves
            US-led force to guard food for Somalia (Dec. 3). North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) signed (Dec.
            17).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1993</pattern>
        <template>Vaclav Havel elected Czech President (Jan. 26). British House of Commons approves European unity pact
            (May 20). Maastricht Treaty takes effect, creating European Union (Nov. 1). Twenty-two UN troops killed in
            Somalia (June 5). Israeli-Palestinian accord reached (Aug. 28). Yeltsin's forces crush revolt in Russian
            Parliament (Oct. 4 et seq.). China breaks nuclear test moratorium (Oct. 5). South Africa adopts majority
            rule constitution (Nov. 18).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1994</pattern>
        <template>Serbs' heavy weapons pound Sarajevo (Jan. 5-6). Thousands dead in Rwanda massacre (April 6). South
            Africa holds first interracial national election (April 29); Nelson Mandela elected President. Israel signs
            accord with Palestinians (May 4), peace treaty with Jordan (Oct. 17). IRA declares cease-fire in Northern
            Ireland (Aug. 31). Ulster Protestants declare cease-fire (Oct. 13). Aristide returns to Haiti (Oct. 4),
            forms Government with Prime Minister and full Cabinet (Nov. 9). US sends forces to Persian Gulf (Oct. 7).
            Russians attack secessionist Republic of Chechnya (Dec. 11 et seq.).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1995</pattern>
        <template>US rescues Mexico's economy with $20-billion aid program (Feb. 21). Russian space station Mir greets
            first Americans (March 14). US shuttle docks with station (June 27). Nerve gas attack in Tokyo subway kills
            eight and injures thousands. The Aum Shinrikyo ("Supreme Truth") cult is to blame (March 20). Death toll
            2,000 in Rwanda massacre (April 22). Fighting escalates in Bosnia and Croatia (May 1). Warring parties agree
            on cease-fire (Oct. 5); sign peace treaty (Dec. 14). France explodes nuclear device in Pacific; wide
            protests ensue (Sept. 5). Israelis and Palestinians agree on transferring West Bank to Arabs (Sept. 24).
            Israeli Prime Minister Yitzhak Rabin slain by Jewish extremist at peace rally (Nov. 4).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1996</pattern>
        <template>Chechens capture 2,000 Russians (Jan. 9). Chechnya peace treaty signed (May 27). France agrees to end
            nuclear testing (Jan. 29). Britain alarmed by an outbreak of "mad cow" disease (March 20 et seq.). UN
            tribunal charges war crimes by Bosnian Muslims and Croats (March 22). Nations pledge $1.23 billion in aid to
            rebuild Bosnia (April 22). South Africa gets new constitution (May 8). Israel elects Benjamin Netanyahu as
            prime minister (May 31). Militant Taliban leaders seize Afghan capital of Kabul (Sept. 27). Iraqis strike at
            Kurdish enclave (Aug. 31); after warning, US attacks Iraq's southern air defenses (Sept. 2–3). Ethnic
            violence breaks out in Zairian refugee camps (Oct. 13); Clinton approves plan for UN-backed relief mission
            for 1.2 million Hutu refugees starving in eastern Zaire (Nov. 13). Hundreds of thousands return to Rwanda
            (Nov. 15–18).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1997</pattern>
        <template>Hebron agreement signed; Israel gives up large part of West Bank city of Hebron (Jan. 16). Israeli
            government approves establishment of Jewish settlement in East Jerusalem, a setback in Middle East peace
            process (Feb. 26). US, UK, and France agree to freeze Nazis' gold loot (Feb. 3). Hong Kong returns to
            Chinese rule (June 30). Khmer Rouge hold trial of longtime leader Pol Pot (July 25). Swiss plan first
            payment to Holocaust victims (Sept. 17). European Union plans to admit six nations (Dec. 13).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1998</pattern>
        <template>Serbs battle ethnic Albanians in Kosovo (March 5 et seq.). Serbs renew attack on Kosovo rebels (June
            1). NATO, on verge of air strikes, reaches settlement with Milosevic on Kosovo (Oct. 12). Good Friday Accord
            is reached in Northern Ireland (April 10). Irish Parliament backs peace agreement (April 22). Europeans
            agree on single currency, the euro (May 3). India conducts three atomic tests despite worldwide disapproval
            (May 11, 13). Pakistan stages five nuclear tests in response (May 29, 30). Indonesian dictator Suharto steps
            down after 32 years in power (May 21). US embassies in Kenya and Tanzania bombed (Aug. 7). US cruise
            missiles hit suspected terrorist bases in Sudan and Afghanistan (Aug. 20). Russia fights to avert financial
            collapse (Aug. 17). Former Chilean dictator Augusto Pinochet arrested in London (Oct. 16). Wye Mills
            Agreement between Netanyahu and Arafat moves Middle East peace talks forward (Oct. 23). Iraq ends
            cooperation with UN arms inspectors (Aug. 5). Clinton orders air strikes (Dec. 16–19).
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 1999</pattern>
        <template>Russian president Boris Yeltsin survives impeachment hearings (May), reshuffles his cabinet twice
            (May, Aug.), and takes military action against Islamic separatists in Dagestan and Chechnya. Nelson Mandela,
            first black president of South Africa, steps down (June 16), and Thabo Mbeki takes over. War erupts in
            Kosovo after Yugoslavia's president Slobodan Milosevic clamps down on the province, massacring and deporting
            ethnic Albanians. NATO begins Operation Allied Force on March 24, 1999, launching air strikes against
            Belgrade for 78 consecutive days until Milosevic relents. Background: Timeline: The Splintering of Kosovo
            and Timeline: NATO in Kosovo. Magnitude 7.4 earthquake kills more than 15,600 and leaves 600,000 homeless in
            Turkey (Aug. 17). East Timor population votes for independence from Indonesia (Aug. 30, 1999), which causes
            pro-Indonesian forces to massacre and uproot thousands of East Timorese. Pakistani government is overthrown
            in the midst of economic strife and intensified fighting with India over Kashmir (Oct. 12). The world awaits
            the consequences of the Y2K bug, with more drastic millennial theorists warning of Armageddon.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT HAPPENED IN 2000</pattern>
        <template>Austria at center of European dispute after conservative People's Party forms coalition with the
            far-right Freedom Party, headed by xenophobe Jörg Haider (Feb. 3). Reformists win control of Iranian
            parliament for first time since 1979 Islamic revolution (Feb. 26). Governing of Northern Ireland passes back
            and forth between Britain and nascent Northern Irish parliament; major dispute over IRA's refusal to disarm
            (Feb-May). Former Indonesian president Suharto under house arrest, charged with corruption and abuse of
            power (May 29). Presidents of North and South Korea sign peace accord, and at least symbolically, end a
            half-century of antagonism (June 13). Vicente Fox Quesada elected president of Mexico, ending 71 years of
            one-party rule by the Institutional Revolutionary Party (PRI) (July 2). Concorde crash kills 113 near Paris
            (July 25). Palestinians and Israelis clash, spurred by visit of right-wing Israeli leader Ariel Sharon to a
            joint Jewish/Muslim holy site; "Al Aksa intifada" continues unabated (Sept. 30 et seq.). Nationwide uprising
            overthrows Yugoslavian president Milosevic (Oct. 5); Vojislav Kostunica sworn in as president (Oct. 7). U.S.
            sailors on Navy destroyer Cole die in Yemen terrorist explosion (Oct. 12). Mad cow disease alarms Europe
            (Nov. 30 et seq.).
        </template>
    </category>
</aiml>